<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Richmond Real Estate Video Blog with Mark Adams</title>
    <description>Our mission at Mark Adams &amp; Associates is to be your best resource for Richmond real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Mark Adams &amp; Associates, your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 11:21:56 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 11:21:56 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>January 2021 Richmond home price update</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/adams-fb.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friends and Clients —&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real estate market continues to surge ahead. However, clouds might be forming on the horizon for sellers. Let me give you the details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Ultra-low mortgage rates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout 2020, the popular 30-year fixed mortgage rate set 15 new record lows. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It ended 2020 just one basis point higher than the latest record low and currently stands at 2.86%, a full percentage point lower than one year ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These ultra-low mortgage rates are driving an increase in demand. Unfortunately, sales are restricted due to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Record-low inventory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were just 1.28 million homes available for sale at the end of November, the last month for which we have full data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is down 22% from a year earlier. It is also the lowest inventory count since the National Association of Realtors began tracking this metric in 1982.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, home prices are shooting up thanks to strong demand and record low inventory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The median price of an existing home sold in November was a staggering 14.6% higher than in November 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re worried this pace is unsustainable, you might be right:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. A change in the market?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some experts warn that home prices are overheating and that affordability is suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They might have a point because, after five consecutive months of gains, closed sales of existing homes lowered in November. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, after three straight months of record highs, homebuilder confidence in December dropped 4%. December mortgage applications also fell. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So what does this all mean for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, things might get harder soon for home sellers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lower affordability could hurt demand, and the price growth we’ve seen over the past months might slow down, or prices might decrease like we started to see before the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, nationwide trends haven’t caught up to us yet in Richmond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demand is still very strong.&lt;/strong&gt; If you were to list now, you could sell quickly and at top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to get an idea of what your home is worth right now, you can use the following home value calculator, which is based on recent Richmond sales:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://markadamsblog.com/homevalue/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Enter your address here to find out what your home is currently worth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are considering selling while the current market lasts, give me a call at &lt;strong&gt;804.237.8585.&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve helped many people sell in these pandemic circumstances, and I’m here to answer your questions and help however I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a friend or family member thinking about selling it would be my pleasure to earn their business. Don’t hesitate to call me and I promise to take great care of them.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great day,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark Adams&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/january-2021-richmond-home-price-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/january-2021-richmond-home-price-update.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: What Are Your Good Luck Superstitions?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qOmDuz4kqZU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;You may not be superstitious, but we’re at least a little ‘stitious!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got together as a team to celebrate another successful year in business, in spite of all the curveballs 2020 threw our way. Although it was a great year for many reasons, you might be as happy as we are to say “good riddance!” to 2020. As our mindsets shift toward 2021, we want to bring about &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the good fortune possible, so we reminisced on some superstitions from our childhoods. We figure that 2021 may need as many of these good-luck charms and superstitions as it can get, so we went ahead and performed a whole mess of them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start, &lt;strong&gt;Mark’s mom always prepared black-eyed peas to eat on New Year’s to bring good luck.&lt;/strong&gt; He also eats an apple every day to keep the doctor away (would you call that luck or science?).  Also, picking up pennies is something he still does to this day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chloe also recalls tossing pennies into a fountain as a kid for good luck, and on the first day of every month, &lt;strong&gt;she recites the words “bunny, bunny, bunny”—a twist on the classic “rabbit, rabbit, rabbit” superstition.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=People in Spain toast at midnight with 12 grapes in their glass, symbolizing 12 months of good luck for the new year.%20http://localhost:4000/q-what-are-your-good-luck-superstitions.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“People in Spain toast at midnight with 12 grapes in their glass, symbolizing 12 months of good luck for the new year.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rabbits are also a part of Amy’s good luck traditions. She carries a rabbit’s foot to rub for good luck, with much success; it’s brought about some clutch UVA basketball wins and even a surprise baby!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lisa has a horseshoe from her grandfather that symbolizes luck, and tosses salt over her shoulder. She also knocks on wood, which is something you might do all the time, too, but do you know why? &lt;strong&gt;In Irish folklore, evil spirits live in the wood, so you must knock on it to deafen their ears to your wishes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, we all decided to cheers to the new year. As it turns out, Spaniards toast at midnight with 12 grapes in their glass; each one is to be eaten to symbolize 12 months of good luck in the upcoming year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s to your good fortune in 2021! If we can help you with that, at least by way of your real estate needs, please don’t hesitate to reach out. Happy holidays to you and yours, and adios, 2020!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-what-are-your-good-luck-superstitions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-what-are-your-good-luck-superstitions.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: How Can You Stay Safe This Holiday Season?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ijFyfHHp7uc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Officer Mashburn shares some simple but important tips for holiday safety.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Tis the season to be jolly! Let’s prevent some criminal folly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We stole some of Officer Mashburn’s time, but we promise it was for a good cause.&lt;/strong&gt; She joined us to answer some questions about deterring crime during the holiday season. Curious what you could take away from her message? Check out our brief interview in the video above to learn some great tips on protecting your deliveries from “porch pirates,” as well as protecting yourself, your home, and your vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re just looking for quick tips to snatch ‘n grab, here are the highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Leave special instructions for delivery drivers for where to place your packages; ask that they hide them behind outdoor furniture or leave them at a side door where they are less visible.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Keep all of your doors/windows locked at all times! &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Don’t leave valuables (shopping bags, presents, etc.) in your car. Take them inside.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Leave your lights on, especially your outdoor lights. Sure, it might run up your electric bill, but on the plus side, Santa will have no problem finding your house!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to Officer Mashburn for spending time with us and for serving our communities. &lt;strong&gt;Even during this busy time of year, we’ll be here to help with any real estate needs you may have.&lt;/strong&gt; Happy holidays, and stay safe, friends!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 08:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-how-can-you-stay-safe-this-holiday-season.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-how-can-you-stay-safe-this-holiday-season.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Are You Thankful for This Year?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/34MLnWGVSmo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Mark Adams Team is grateful for so many things this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the holidays approaching, it’s a great time to pause and reflect on what we’re grateful for. &lt;strong&gt;Today I’m joined by my favorite people, my team, to share what we’re thankful for this holiday season.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amy is thankful to have been able to spend a lot more time at home with her family this year. She has also gotten to enjoy decorating her new home in Wintergreen. Her children have been very productive in making ornaments for their Christmas tree at the mountain house. These talented kiddos need their own Etsy account!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chloe is grateful for many things that came from quarantine. She’s gotten to fulfill her dream of being a stay-at-home mom while also having a job—the best of both worlds. She’s also thankful for all the educators who have taken an impossible situation and made the best of it. Although homeschooling is challenging, she is glad to have a more active role in Joie’s education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We hope that you and yours have a truly happy Thanksgiving.%20http://localhost:4000/what-are-you-thankful-for-this-year.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We hope that you and yours have a truly happy Thanksgiving.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fall is Lisa’s favorite time of the year, and is grateful that she’s had the opportunity to spend lots of time with her animals in 2020. She’s thankful for her health and the ability to work from home with her husband (thanks to noise-canceling headphones). She was also given an unusual blessing in the fact that her brother and his family were able to spend more time with their mother, who passed away recently. The hospital allowed his whole family to be there with her, which isn’t typical these days. Also, Lisa is grateful for being able to spend time with friends over Zoom, take walks, and settle into a good book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for me, I’m thankful for my friends and family members. This time in quarantine has also given me an opportunity to not only spend more time at home, but also to enjoy the amazing garden my wife created where she’s grown some impressive pumpkins! One of the most critical lessons we’ve learned during quarantine is how important it is to be around people. Our team has missed meeting in person on a regular basis, so we really appreciate this time we’ve had together today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last, but not least, we’re all thankful for you!&lt;/strong&gt; We’re so grateful for being able to serve such amazing people like yourselves&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; We hope that you and yours have a truly happy Thanksgiving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you thankful for this year? Reach out to us and let us know—we’d love to hear about it!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-are-you-thankful-for-this-year.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-are-you-thankful-for-this-year.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our Blind Taste Test of All Things Pumpkin</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/epHueuztr2I?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;In honor of fall, we’re (blindly) sampling savory pumpkin-flavored treats.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may have heard of Blind Melon; please welcome Blind Pumpkin to the stage—a blind pumpkin taste test, that is! ‘Tis the season for all things pumpkin spice. We decided to take a break from work and go ALL in. Our buddy, Greg Cowart of NFM Lending, joined Mark and Amy to sample a spread of pumpkin-flavored novelties dished out by Lisa and Chloe (who may have snuck in some mind games). Check out this video to see our reactions, reviews, and see which of us has the sharpest palette.  And now that the sugar coma has worn off, we’re back to work, so don’t hesitate to give us a shout for your real estate needs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, thanks for watching!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/our-blind-taste-test-of-all-things-pumpkin.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/our-blind-taste-test-of-all-things-pumpkin.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: How do you know if refinancing is right for you?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CK7uEyzsgUU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Given the market, should you stay in your home and refinance or just sell it?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you stay in your current house and refinance or should you prepare to sell it because the market is so attractive for sellers right now? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are a couple of questions you’ll need to ask yourself before you can make this decision:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How long will I stay in the area? &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What does it cost to refinance?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have the answers to those questions, choosing which path is right for you should be a little easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s talk about the refinancing process. A good rule of thumb is that if you can get a good interest rate that’s 1% lower than your current interest rate, it might make sense to refinance. Typically, there are fees associated with refinancing. To find out what those fees are, just &lt;strong&gt;ask your mortgage company for a good faith estimate.&lt;/strong&gt; That will have a list of all the fees associated with refinancing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you can get a good interest rate that’s 1% lower than your current interest rate, it might make sense to refinance.%20http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-know-if-refinancing-is-right-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you can get a good interest rate that’s 1% lower than your current interest rate, it might make sense to refinance.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suppose that it’s going to cost $2,000 to refinance your house. In this scenario, you’ll get a 1% reduction in your interest rate, so you’d save $100 a month on your mortgage if you do refinance. In this case, it would take you 20 months to pay off the $2,000 investment. Ask yourself if it makes sense to even invest your money right now if it’ll take that long to recoup. &lt;strong&gt;It might make more sense to use that money to fix your house up&lt;/strong&gt; so that when you get ready to sell in two or three years, you’ll get top dollar for it. It just depends on your situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re still not sure about which path is right for you, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to share my advice about what exactly you can do to your house to get the biggest bang for your buck. I can also give you guidance about whether it makes sense to refinance your house instead. It’s my pleasure to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-know-if-refinancing-is-right-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-know-if-refinancing-is-right-for-you.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: Do You Know a Small Business Owner?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3OAXnhesBPk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s how we’re helping other small businesses in our community grow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lisa and I started our business 21 years ago, and we quickly learned we had no idea how to run a small business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I sought out information at a real estate conference, where I met a coach who told me something that has stuck with me after all these years: &lt;strong&gt;“If you’re going to be a business owner, you need to make personal growth a part of your routine for the rest of your life.” &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We will be offering training, networking, and much more.%20http://localhost:4000/q-do-you-know-a-small-business-owner.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We will be offering training, networking, and much more.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years later, I met another speaker who introduced me to the idea of masterminding. I learned how important it is to seek out other business owners in my field so that we can share experiences and learn from one another with the common goal of elevating ourselves and our industry. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;That’s the purpose of the &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/453620405315147v&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;group I started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;on Facebook, Intentional Business Owners of RVA.&lt;/strong&gt; We will be offering training on business and personal growth, networking opportunities, and promoting your business connections via individual spotlights. If you are a small business owner, or know someone who is, we would love to have you be a part of our new community. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 12:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-do-you-know-a-small-business-owner.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-do-you-know-a-small-business-owner.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want to know what your home is worth for free?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you been thinking about what your home is worth lately?&lt;br /&gt;I wanted to let you know Richmond home prices are not dropping in spite of the seemingly never ending curve balls 2020 is throwing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, while inventory is down 40% nationally since sellers are likely hesitant to have buyers walk through their home, home prices are still strong (if not stronger).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you like to know what your home here in Richmond is worth for free? &lt;strong&gt;Call me at 804-237-8585.&lt;/strong&gt; You’ll get my recommended home value opinion at no charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just need a quick phone call with you to learn more about your home, along with any photos or videos you can send me (very important) by email, text, FB Messenger, etc. You’ll have a better idea of what a bank may value your home for a refinance, you can update your balance sheet, or you can just rest assured knowing what a buyer would likely pay today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Just last month, we worked with two families whose homes sold for 8% and 14% over the list price. You can imagine how pleased these clients were!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interest rates are at record lows after the Federal Reserve lowered their lending rate and bank reserve requirements. This keeps home prices high since money is cheap for borrowers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History shows this amazing trend won’t go on forever. If you’re thinking about selling your home, &lt;strong&gt;this summer/fall may be your best chance to land your highest selling price.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m here to help with any real estate needs you have. Let me know if you have any questions. I’ll give you a well-researched and accurate answer so you can make the right decisions. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 16:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/want-to-know-what-your-home-is-worth-for-free.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/want-to-know-what-your-home-is-worth-for-free.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Friends Are My Friends</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ja2nrMjXVxE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;We want to assist your family and friends too. Help us help them!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know by now that our team’s motto is “Where Relationships Are Key!”. We don’t spend hours a day on the Internet searching for strangers who want to buy or sell real estate. Our focus is on providing five-star service to our clients from start to finish and beyond in order to build positive, lasting relationships. &lt;strong&gt;Our goal is to treat people so well that they wouldn’t hesitate to suggest our professional care to their family and friends.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We learned a long time ago that if you take care of people, they’ll take care of you. So I’m asking you now: Will you help me help the people you love? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have friends or family needing assistance with real estate, our team of specialists is ready to support them. We are just a call, text, or email away. We would love to help!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 14:05:12 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/your-friends-are-my-friends.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/your-friends-are-my-friends.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>August Is Hot, But the Market Is Hotter</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2vIxx0JxnGI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our real estate market is red-hot for sellers right now.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I’m not big on predictions when it comes to the real estate market, but I am big on giving you statistical data directly from our Richmond Metro MLS so you know what’s specifically happening right now. &lt;strong&gt;The three things you need to know before you get ready to sell are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Average days on market.&lt;/strong&gt; Right now, that number is 28 days in Richmond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Average list-to-sale-price ratio.&lt;/strong&gt; This is 100% right now, meaning that sellers are getting full price for their homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Inventory.&lt;/strong&gt; We have only 1.3 months right now. To give you some perspective, a seller’s market is anything under six months and a buyer’s market is anything over six months. With just 1.3 months, we have an extreme seller’s market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I’ve never seen a market like this before.%20http://localhost:4000/august-is-hot-but-the-market-is-hotter.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I’ve never seen a market like this before.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This checks out when it comes to what we’ve been experiencing with our clients. We’re working with one seller right now who got an offer that was 15% above asking price. Another seller got a sight-unseen cash offer of 8% over their list price. It’s a crazy market, and I’ve never seen anything like this in 21 years in the business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re even entertaining the idea of selling your home right now, I would love to give you some advice on how to proceed. Just give me a call or send me an email today with any questions you might have. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 10:30:01 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/august-is-hot-but-the-market-is-hotter.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/august-is-hot-but-the-market-is-hotter.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
