<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Richmond Real Estate Video Blog with Mark Adams</title>
    <description>Our mission at Mark Adams &amp; Associates is to be your best resource for Richmond real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Mark Adams &amp; Associates, your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 12:29:12 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 12:29:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inspect Your Fire Extinguishers</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qzJw3UqgBiI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to talk about fire extinguisher safety and inspections. When I was doing my research on this topic, the first thing I did was look at my fire extinguishers to see if they were safe, full, and able to be used correctly. As it turns out, mine weren’t. Do you remember the last time you checked yours? I have a few helpful tips I learned that I wanted to share with you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, when you store your fire extinguisher, the information needs to face the outside so the user can see it when they’re grabbing the canister. You’ll also notice a little safety pin on the top - this is what keeps you from accidentally depressing the fire extinguisher. There’s also a gauge that shows how full your extinguisher is. Now keep in mind, just because the canister is full, that doesn’t mean the extinguisher is still effective. They do have expiration dates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years and exchanged for a new one. I did some shopping online, and I found that &lt;strong&gt;they are usually between $20 to $30&lt;/strong&gt; and can even be bought in packages. Some now come in a smaller form that is perfect to keep in the kitchen. The smaller ones are about the size of an aerosol can, and they’re designed to spray a small fire on your cooktop, but a larger one should still be kept close by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years.%20http://localhost:4000/inspect-your-fire-extinguishers.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know there are three classes of fire extinguishers? Class A is for wood or paper products, class B is for liquids, and class C is for electrical fires. When you’re buying your fire extinguisher, you want to get an A, B, and C class fire extinguisher for your kitchen. If you like candles or have a fireplace in the house you should have another fire extinguisher nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you found this information valuable. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me by phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/inspect-your-fire-extinguishers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/inspect-your-fire-extinguishers.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inspect Your Fire Extinguishers</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qzJw3UqgBiI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’ll talk about fire extinguisher safety and inspections. When I was doing my research on this topic, the first thing I did was look at my fire extinguishers to see if they were safe, full, and able to be used correctly. I discovered that mine weren’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned that when you store your fire extinguisher, the information needs to face the outside so the user can see it when they’re grabbing the canister. The little safety pin keeps from you accidentally depressing the fire extinguisher. There’s also a gauge that shows how full your extinguisher is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years and exchanged for a new one. &lt;strong&gt;They are usually between $20 to $30&lt;/strong&gt; and can even be bought in packages. Some now come in a smaller form that is perfect to keep in the kitchen. The smaller ones are about the size of an aerosol can, and they’re designed to spray a small fire on your cooktop, but a larger one should still be close by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years.%20http://localhost:4000/fire-extinguisher-safety-and-inspections.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are three classes of fire extinguishers; Class A is for wood or paper products, class B is for liquids, and class C is for electrical fires. When you’re buying your fire extinguisher, you want to get an A, B, and C class fire extinguisher for your kitchen. If you like candles or have a fireplace in the house you should have another fire extinguisher nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you found this information valuable. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me by phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/fire-extinguisher-safety-and-inspections.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/fire-extinguisher-safety-and-inspections.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Sellers and Buyers Can Navigate Our Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/T9Zj_4YMC_E?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Comparing today’s market to January 2021 and what the numbers mean for you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to know what’s going on in real estate? Today we’ll be looking at data from Central Virginia’s MLS, which covers single-family homes, townhouses, and condos. I’ll mostly be comparing data from 2021 to 2022 so that we can see how things have changed over the last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The median sales price in January of 2021 was $285,500, and in January 2022, it was $316,250. That’s an increase of about 13%. Meanwhile, the median sales price jumped from $321,000 to $362,000.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In January of 2021, we had 1,991 new homes hit the market, while we only had 1,596 in 2022. This means &lt;strong&gt;fewer people are putting their homes on the market.&lt;/strong&gt; 1,531 houses closed in 2021, while in 2022, our area had 1,443 closings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you’re looking to sell, now might be the best time. %20http://localhost:4000/how-sellers-and-buyers-can-navigate-our-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you’re looking to sell, now might be the best time. ”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for days on market, we had an average of around seven in January of 2021, and it’s the same now. However, this number is a little misleading. If you price your home correctly and work with a great team, you can easily sell your home in a day or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does this all mean for you?&lt;/strong&gt; We know interest rates are increasing, and buyers seem frustrated with rising prices. When rates do increase, prices will probably have to go down, so if you’re looking to sell, now might be the best time. Meanwhile, buyers will want to purchase a house before rates hike since even small rate increases hurt their buying power quite a bit. Are you interested in searching for available homes in the RVA area? You can access any MLS listing here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://markadams.exprealty.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://markadams.exprealty.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team is currently sitting on 15 buyers desperate to buy a home before rates increase. If you are looking to buy or sell, please call or email us. We’d love to help you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-sellers-and-buyers-can-navigate-our-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-sellers-and-buyers-can-navigate-our-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are You Prepared for a Home Emergency?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mSyGBA6p65Y?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s a quick story about why it’s important to prepare for emergencies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I have a story I wanted to share with you about something that recently happened to a friend of mine. (Disclaimer: Everyone is fine!) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While my friend was out of town with his family, his house caught on fire. What’s worse is that his pets were stuck inside. Thankfully, the neighbors knew about my friend’s pets, and they were able to get the animals out safely before the fire department arrived. When Lisa and I heard about this, we thought, “Wow, we really need to get in touch with our neighbors!” Lisa reached out to them to ask how many pets they have in their homes, and she let them know how many we have in ours. &lt;strong&gt;This exchange of information could be very important if, God forbid, an emergency happened in your neighborhood.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Always overestimate how much time you will be out of your home so that you can plan your temporary accommodations accordingly.%20http://localhost:4000/are-you-prepared-for-a-home-emergency.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Always overestimate how much time you will be out of your home so that you can plan your temporary accommodations accordingly.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, Lisa and I had a pipe freeze in our house, and the whole place flooded. We lost nearly everything, including both of our computers, which held so much important data. At the time, cloud storage wasn’t available, but I can tell you now that we make sure to back up our important documents and information regularly. &lt;strong&gt;I can’t speak enough about how crucial it is to make sure your vital information is safe from fire or flood.&lt;/strong&gt; I also encourage you to check out my video about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H3KJvHSCXtA&amp;amp;list=UUZbv1oVEFX4aT5s4K-9-v6A&amp;amp;index=56&quot;&gt;making a digital home inventory&lt;/a&gt;, just in case. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My final tip concerns your insurance company. When our house flooded, the insurance company told us we would be out of our home for about 3 months. It actually turned out to be 10 months! Thankfully, we were renting an apartment with a renewable, month-to-month lease. The bottom line: Always overestimate how much time you will be out of your home so that you can plan your temporary accommodations accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope these tips for preparing your home for a potential emergency are helpful. I wish you all a safe and happy new year, and as always, if you need any assistance with anything real estate-related, give me a call or send me an email. I’d be happy to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-you-prepared-for-a-home-emergency.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/are-you-prepared-for-a-home-emergency.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our Tips For Reviving Your Home in 2022</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/7mTmLSjrlkc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here are our tips for maintaining and refreshing your home in 2022. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year! It’s the time of year when everyone is making a list of what they want to get done with their home, and I have some great tips to help you accomplish your goals. Lisa and I do this exercise every year, so we want to go over how we revive our home:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Wipe down your shower after every use.&lt;/strong&gt; This will prevent mold from building up, so you won’t have to remove it later. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Re-caulk your shower.&lt;/strong&gt; Unfortunately, wiping down your shower won’t prevent the caulk from turning yellow. If you replace the caulk, you’d be surprised how new your shower will look. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Spray your glass shower door with Rain-X every three months.&lt;/strong&gt; This will prevent water and soap scum from sticking to your shower door. It will look brand-new all year round. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Change your home decor every three months.&lt;/strong&gt; Lisa changes our decor based on the season. Her tip for you is that instead of buying new pillows, she simply buys new pillowcases. This way, we get a fresh, seasonal look without breaking the bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Subtle changes to your home can make it really pop. %20http://localhost:4000/our-tips-for-maintaining-your-home-in-2022.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Subtle changes to your home can make it really pop. ”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Replace the front door mat regularly.&lt;/strong&gt; These things don’t last as long as you’d think. If your mat is looking old, consider replacing it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Replace the mailbox and replace the post.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s subtle, but little things like this can make a big impact on your home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Replace the pots for houseplants, and replace your picture frames.&lt;/strong&gt; This tip is similar to changing pillowcases. You can make the details of your home seem new and exciting just by changing how they’re framed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Make sure the lightbulbs are the same type and color.&lt;/strong&gt; This will make your home appear more cohesive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. Install switch plate covers.&lt;/strong&gt; This way, you don’t have to replace the receptacle ever again. The convenience switch plate covers offer is unmatched. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, these tips gave you some ideas on how to breathe new life into your home in 2022. If you have a tip you’d like to share with me, leave it in the chat or send me an email. I’d love to share it with everyone else!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/our-tips-for-maintaining-your-home-in-2022.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/our-tips-for-maintaining-your-home-in-2022.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What We Accomplished in 2021</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/THxi_VITS3M?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here are some of our biggest highlights from a jam-packed 2021. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy holidays! Lisa and I love this time of year because it gives us an opportunity to reflect on what we’ve accomplished. Not only that, but we learn from what we did to make next year even better. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, one of our goals for 2021 was to build Lisa an amazing garden, and we accomplished it. Lisa wanted us to eat better, and our garden has been providing us with tons of vegetables. &lt;strong&gt;Since we share, all our neighbors are pretty happy with us, too!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re like me, then you remember all those great meals you had as a kid that you  haven’t had in a long time. I wanted to spend more time with my mom this year, so I started going over to her home for dinner more often. We had some of the classic food from my childhood, but we tried some excellent new dishes, as well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also had to go on many business trips this year. Typically, I do what I need to do for business and leave, but this year, I made an effort to explore each new area I visited. For example, I went hiking in Arizona, and the terrain was unlike anything I had seen before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Teaching shop has been the highlight of my week ever since I started doing it.%20http://localhost:4000/what-we-accomplished-in-2021.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Teaching shop has been the highlight of my week ever since I started doing it.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually, Lisa and I aren’t big spenders, but I had been talking recently about how I wanted a new truck. When she took her truck to the dealership to be serviced, she found almost exactly what I had been looking for, and she surprised me with the vehicle when she came home. This wasn’t on our list of goals, but it was an awesome surprise and certainly a highlight of the year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something that’s important to me and Lisa is service. Recently, I had the opportunity to help teach a shop class for a local school. I was super excited, and it’s been the highlight of my week ever since I started doing it. Helping kids learn something I love has been incredibly rewarding, and &lt;strong&gt;I look forward to teaching the class in the future. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we look forward to 2022, one of the highlights for Lisa and I will be our 32-year wedding anniversary. It’s hard to believe it’s been that long, but I’ve loved spending my life with her. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, that’s enough about us; let us know what you are looking forward to in 2022. Just give us a call or shoot us an email. We look forward to hearing from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-we-accomplished-in-2021.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-we-accomplished-in-2021.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Holidays</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Real Estate Market Update to Round Out 2021</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NzZFLIG-4W4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s a brief end-of-year real estate market update for Central Virginia.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we head toward the end of the year, I’m sharing how our real estate market is doing and where we’re headed in 2022. We’re going directly into the Central Virginia Regional MLS to look at some of the latest numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let’s start with the average sale price.&lt;/strong&gt; At the beginning of 2021, it was at $321,733. It precipitously rose through the middle of the year, and we hit a high of $367,966 in the summer before dropping back down later into the year. Right now, it sits right around $359,000. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom line is that our lack of inventory is the cause behind these price increases. In January 2020, we sold 4,001 homes. In January 2021, we sold only 2,126. &lt;strong&gt;The big reason behind this is that there just weren’t as many homes available for buyers to purchase.&lt;/strong&gt; That drove prices up, and that inventory doesn’t look like it will go back up anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t know where the market is going, but we do know that it’s definitely changing. The list-to-sale price ratio measures what homes have sold for compared to their original list prices. In January, we were a little over 100%. Then in May, we jumped up to 104%. Then it started to gradually go down, and now we’re at 101.5%. That’s a tell-tale sign of the market softening and changing. &lt;strong&gt;I don’t know where it’s going, but I do know one thing: Sale prices are very strong.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you're a buyer, you can still take advantage of rates in the 3.2% range.%20http://localhost:4000/a-real-estate-market-update-to-end-2021.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you’re a buyer, you can still take advantage of rates in the 3.2% range.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the thing: I believe we’ll see the same type of activity as we go into 2022 based on the fact that there still aren’t a lot of available properties for sale. If you’re a seller, the positive is that you’re probably going to get a very high price for your house. We have data that shows it’s a great time to get your home sold for top dollar. If you’re a buyer, you can still take advantage of rates in the 3.2% range.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to sell and buy, how can you set it up so you’re successful? &lt;strong&gt;We’ve had a lot of success selling properties off-market.&lt;/strong&gt; We found buyers for many of our sellers without having to put their homes on the market. These buyers can meet the seller’s needs in price and flexibility to give them the time to find their new home. This situation puts you in a great position as a buyer because your home is already sold. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about selling, I’d be happy to do a Comparitive Market Analysis and let you know what your home is worth today. I might already have a buyer in my back pocket who can give you what you’re looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about these numbers, the market, or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-real-estate-market-update-to-end-2021.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-real-estate-market-update-to-end-2021.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thanks for Coming To the Zoo With Us!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vPHBc82FDj0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here are some highlights and clips from our fifth annual zoo event.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for coming out to our fifth annual zoo event. &lt;strong&gt;We had a great time seeing all of our amazing clients and walking around the Metro Richmond Zoo.&lt;/strong&gt; While we were there, we also collected a ton of food for &lt;a href=&quot;https://feedmore.org/&quot;&gt;Feed More&lt;/a&gt;. We put together a short highlight reel of the event. Check it out in the video above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, give us a call if you have any questions. We’d love to help, and thanks again for coming out to the zoo with us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/thanks-for-coming-to-the-zoo-with-us.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/thanks-for-coming-to-the-zoo-with-us.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy Thanksgiving From Mark Adams &amp; Associates</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/erl7ha9OHCc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s why we’re so thankful for you as we reflect on this past year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you, thank you, thank you! Words aren’t enough to express my gratitude for all of you, but I’m going to try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lisa and I sit down every year around this time and think about the biggest blessings that have come our way over the last year. The last 12 months have been weird at best, and we know many business owners that are unfortunately no longer in business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because of you, not only did we have a great year, but we thrived in this strange environment.&lt;/strong&gt; We can’t thank you enough for your support. There are people that work for us who rely on us and have families, and there are other real estate-adjacent companies that rely on us as well. All of them have been positively affected by you and your trust in us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Your trust and support mean the world to us.%20http://localhost:4000/happy-thanksgiving-from-mark-adams-associates.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Your trust and support mean the world to us.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We know how emotional it is to buy a house.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s typically the single biggest investment you’ll ever make. Lisa has told me many stories of watching kids growing up in houses and it always brings us back to the time that we got to serve them. We love seeing the pictures and posts of your families on social media. Some of those young kids are now buying homes with us or referring us to their other family members and friends. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past 21 years, most of our business has been referral-based. From the bottom of our hearts, thank you for that. &lt;strong&gt;If you need anything from us, real estate or not, feel free to reach out because we would absolutely love an opportunity to serve you in any way possible.&lt;/strong&gt; We hope you have an amazing holiday season!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/happy-thanksgiving-from-mark-adams-associates.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/happy-thanksgiving-from-mark-adams-associates.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When Will We Reach the Peak of the Market?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CzmWxaJNtOw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;MLS data is showing us that we’re likely near the peak of the market.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;lt;/p.

&lt;center&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/center&gt;

I get asked a lot about when we’ll know if we’re reaching the peak of this market. I have some statistics from our regional MLS that I want to share with you. I think they give us some idea of where the market’s headed:

**Average sales price.** In January of 2020, the average sales price was around $295,000. In January of 2021, the average sales price was $321,000. In September, the average sales price reached $357,000.

**Homes for sale.** In January of 2020, there were 4,000 homes available. In January of 2021, there were only 2,000. Inventory is really low. In September of 2021, there were still only 2,000 available, when there should normally be 4,000. That's why we continue to see prices go up.

**Days on market.** We had 49 days in January of 2020, 25 days in January of 2021, and 15 days in September of 2021. As far as days on market, it almost halved every step there. That's amazing, right?

&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I think we’re very close to a peak in the market.%20http://localhost:4000/when-will-we-reach-the-peak-of-the-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8220;I think we’re very close to a peak in the market.&amp;#8221;&lt;/a&gt;

**Average list-to-sales price ratio.** This is the statistic that I believe will show us where the market is going. In January of 2020, the average list-to-sales price ratio was 97.5%. In January of 2021, it was 100.2%. In September of 2021, it was almost 102%. However, in May of 2021, it was 104% and declined from then on. I believe that's a tell-tale sign that the market has started to change.

About two months ago, I noticed that we were having fewer showings and offers at the same locations and at the same prices. Those are all signs of buyer fatigue. Buyers are tired and fed up. It's a natural market cycle. Have we hit the peak? I think we're very close to it, but now's still a great time to sell your house for top dollar.

If you're thinking about selling or if you want to know the value of your house, feel free to give me a call. I'd love to help you look at your neighborhood data and learn what's going on to see if you can still sell at or above market value. I look forward to hearing from you.
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/when-will-we-reach-the-peak-of-the-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/when-will-we-reach-the-peak-of-the-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
