<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Richmond Real Estate Video Blog with Mark Adams</title>
    <description>Our mission at Mark Adams &amp; Associates is to be your best resource for Richmond real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Mark Adams &amp; Associates, your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:05:46 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:05:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Truth About Our Housing Market Explained: Richmond’s June Housing Stats </title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/i5A2sXsZrHE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s what buyers and sellers need to know about our housing market. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s going on in our housing market? Things are always changing, so today, I want to share the latest numbers you need to know for the June housing market in Richmond. Let’s delve into the details. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The average sales price stands at nearly $404,000, indicating a slight increase compared to the same period last year. However, the number of new listings entering the market has decreased by 14.2%. To gain a broader perspective, I analyzed data dating back to 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remarkably, this month’s new listings mark the lowest count since 2006.&lt;/strong&gt; As a result, homes are selling for a higher percentage of their asking prices. In the zero to $350,000 price range, properties are typically sold at 98% of the asking price. For homes priced between $351,000 and $650,000, the average sale price exceeds the asking price. And for properties priced at $651,000 and above, the average sale price is 103% above the asking price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The future of our market looks bright. %20http://localhost:4000/the-truth-about-our-housing-market-explained-richmond-s-june-housing-stats.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The future of our market looks bright. ”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is worth noting that we cannot predict when the market dynamics will shift and more inventory will become available. &lt;strong&gt;Currently, we are experiencing the lowest inventory since 2006. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The truth is that no one knows for sure when or how our market will change, but it certainly will again. If you are thinking of buying or selling soon, just call or email us, and we’ll make sure to keep you informed on what’s happening in our market. We look forward to hearing from you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-truth-about-our-housing-market-explained-richmond-s-june-housing-stats.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-truth-about-our-housing-market-explained-richmond-s-june-housing-stats.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Celebrating Our Pets and Community: Highlights From Our Recent Events</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NTq4S6qYrbk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sharing highlights from our recent events, which were fun and fulfilling.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, we’re very excited to share some of the highlights of our recent events. We had such a blast meeting new people and their dogs. Therefore, we wanted to take some time to share some of our favorite moments with you in the video above. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We love to support local animal causes by organizing pack walks, pet food drives, and more. In April, we hosted a pack walk at Dogwood Dell, sponsored the Doggone 5K, 3K, and 1K events at the Pole Green Park, and supported the Richmond Animal League at the 2023 Woofstock event. &lt;strong&gt;Giving back to the community is an important part of our real estate service, and we love to be able to support our furry friends.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy these adorable doggie moments of our recent adventures in the video above—you might even recognize a face or two. Also, if you’re interested in entering the real estate market, remember that we’re here for you and that your support allows us to continue giving back to the community. Call or email us anytime, and we would be happy to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/celebrating-our-pets-and-community-highlights-from-our-recent-pack-walk-event.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/celebrating-our-pets-and-community-highlights-from-our-recent-pack-walk-event.html</guid>
        
        <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Real Estate Market Changes Daily: Stay Informed With Our May Update</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/D3UYdGIG0Gk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;An important update on how much the real estate market is changing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, we’re here with your May market update to help you stay informed so you can make smart real estate decisions. You need to be aware of certain changes, and we’re here with that information. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, &lt;strong&gt;the average sales price is up 10.5%, and new listings are down 13.7% from this time last year.&lt;/strong&gt; Second, when looking at the sales-to-list-price ratio, we can see that it has stayed fairly consistent over the past few months in all price ranges, around 99%. However, things are very different currently, as many properties that have gone under contract in the last 30 days have sold well above the asking price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This shows that the real estate market changes daily, so &lt;strong&gt;it’s important to hire a Realtor who will keep you up to date.&lt;/strong&gt; A lot of people don’t understand the current market because it’s changing so quickly, but we are here to help with that. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The market is changing rapidly.%20http://localhost:4000/the-real-estate-market-changes-daily-stay-informed-with-our-may-update.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The market is changing rapidly.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are thinking about selling, know that the decrease in new listings is driving prices up. Overall, just make sure to &lt;strong&gt;contact us because we can show you what’s going on in your specific neighborhood.&lt;/strong&gt; Then if you want to buy a home, don’t get discouraged. There are still properties out there that are at a good price, and we can help you find them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about today’s market or need help buying or selling, don’t hesitate to reach out. You can call or email us anytime, and we would love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-real-estate-market-changes-daily-stay-informed-with-our-may-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-real-estate-market-changes-daily-stay-informed-with-our-may-update.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don't Let Your Dream Home Slip Away: How to Write an Offer That Stands Out</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wUha0nJv96w?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The secret to winning an offer comes down to these three tips.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re in the market to buy a house, you know how challenging it can be to get your offer accepted. With the real estate market constantly changing, it can be hard to know how to write the best terms for the property you want to purchase. Today we’ll share three tips to help you write the best offer and increase your chances of getting it accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, it’s crucial to &lt;strong&gt;stay on top of the latest market data.&lt;/strong&gt; This will help you determine the right offer price and terms for the specific area you’re interested in. At Mark Adams and Associates, we monitor the data every day, allowing us to provide our clients with informed advice on how to write the best offer for their chosen neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another important step is to &lt;strong&gt;have your agent&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;call the listing agent before you write your offer.&lt;/strong&gt; This will give you valuable insights into the seller’s preferences and the terms they’re looking for. By understanding what’s most important to the seller, you can tailor your offer accordingly, increasing your chances of getting it accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You can increase the chances of getting your offer accepted.%20http://localhost:4000/don-t-let-your-dream-home-slip-away-how-to-write-an-offer-that-stands-out.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You can increase the chances of getting your offer accepted.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, it’s essential to &lt;strong&gt;put all of the information you’ve gathered together to construct the best possible offer.&lt;/strong&gt; By taking the market data and the seller’s preferences into account, you can create a competitive offer that stands out from the rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, if you have any questions about this topic or real estate in general, please feel free to reach out to us by phone or email. We would be happy to help you with all of your real estate needs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/don-t-let-your-dream-home-slip-away-how-to-write-an-offer-that-stands-out.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/don-t-let-your-dream-home-slip-away-how-to-write-an-offer-that-stands-out.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discover the Latest Market Trends in Richmond</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/b0GOP19_SVQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;An overview of the latest Metro Richmond housing market trends.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real estate market is constantly changing, and staying up-to-date on the latest trends and statistics is crucial for buyers, sellers, and agents alike. To help you do this, we’re taking a closer look at the current real estate market in Metro Richmond and sharing some important data that can help you make informed decisions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, &lt;strong&gt;the average sales price in Metro Richmond for March is $400,748.&lt;/strong&gt; This is up by 7.4% from the previous year. However, the number of new listings from the same time last year is down by 12.7%, with only 24,262 new listings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Properties priced from $1 to $350,000 had an average sales price of $252,000 and sellers received an average of $6,000 in concessions, which brought the adjusted sold price to $243,000, or 96% of the original asking price. Also, the properties stayed on the market for an average of 24 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=It's essential to work with an agent who understands the current market trends.%20http://localhost:4000/discover-the-latest-market-trends-in-richmond.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“It’s essential to work with an agent who understands the current market trends.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For properties priced between 351,000 and 650,000, the numbers have remained relatively consistent throughout the year. They’re selling at around 99% of their asking price, with the occasional sale at 98% or 100%. Then for properties priced at 651,000 and above, the market is still strong, with some homes selling above the asking price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The market trends for lower-priced properties suggest that&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;some agents are not doing their due diligence when it comes to researching the market.&lt;/strong&gt; There have been multiple offers on properties in the last 30 days, but some agents are making offers above the asking price without finding out if there are any other offers on the table. This lack of research and education is leading to clients being confused and missing opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to buy or sell a property in Richmond, it’s essential to work with an agent who understands the current market trends and can educate you on what’s happening in your neck of the woods. If you want help with this or want to know exactly how much your house is worth, give us a call and we’ll share this data with you. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/discover-the-latest-market-trends-in-richmond.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/discover-the-latest-market-trends-in-richmond.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Renovate Your Home Without Breaking the Bank</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UwscgGIABf4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our partners can help you renovate your home with minimal stress.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I have some exciting news to share with you! Lately, I’ve been frequently getting asked if renovating the entire house is necessary for selling in the current real estate market. The short answer is that it depends on the location, but I recommend making your house look as nice as possible to get a higher price and sell it faster. In some cases, a full renovation is necessary to get a better return on your investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The good news is that we’ve partnered with a few companies that can do these three things for you: loan you the money, hire the contractors, and manage the project.&lt;/strong&gt; Plus, they won’t charge you a fee, they just have you pay them back when the house sells. It’s a win-win situation! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested, call or email me anytime. I’d be happy to come out and see if this service is right for you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/renovate-your-home-without-breaking-the-bank.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/renovate-your-home-without-breaking-the-bank.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Sellers Need To Know About Today’s Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2Icd15TK43g?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Changes in home prices affect properties in all price ranges.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am excited to share the March edition of the Metro Richmond Real Estate Market Quick Stats with you today. &lt;strong&gt;In the last 30 days, the average sales price and the number of new listings have changed&lt;/strong&gt;, affecting homes in all price ranges, so I am here to keep you up to date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, the average sales price is $351,239, up 6.1% from last year. Secondly, the number of new listings is around 1,399, down 26.8% from last year. This affects all homes differently, so I have split properties into three price ranges. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the $0 to $350,000 price range, the average house came onto the market at $271,500, sold for $261,500, and included $5,050 of concessions. That means the adjusted sold price is $256,450, and the list-to-sold-price ratio is 94%. Lastly, these homes stayed on the market for an average of 24 days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The most opportunity is in the lower price range.%20http://localhost:4000/what-sellers-need-to-know-about-today-s-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The most opportunity is in the lower price range.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know that values aren’t going down, so these stats show us that &lt;strong&gt;sellers are contributing more and more to the buyers’ costs.&lt;/strong&gt; However, this isn’t the same in every price range—in the $351,000 to $650,000 price range, the list-to-sold-price ratio is 98%, and in the $651,000 and up price range, the ratio is 101%. Plus, the numbers have stayed very similar over the last few months in these two ranges, while it has changed more in the first price range. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Typically, when you have a lack of inventory, as we do, that keeps the prices higher. This shows more in the two higher price ranges, while there is the most opportunity in the lower one. Since sellers know they’re going to have to compromise to sell their houses, buyers will have more opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If your house is in the lower price range and you’re considering selling, I recommend getting your home on the market sooner rather than later.&lt;/strong&gt; Act before the list-to-sold-price ratio continues to drop. If your house is in one of the higher price ranges, you’ll get close to asking price, if not more, so you have more time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to know what your property is worth and what a buyer might pay for it, call me anytime! I would be happy to look at the numbers in your neighborhood and share that information with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-sellers-need-to-know-about-today-s-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-sellers-need-to-know-about-today-s-market.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How To Save Money When Selling Your Home</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/1rOB9ZBdfLg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Having your HVAC serviced could save you thousands of dollars.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have an older air conditioning unit and are debating whether or not to replace it before putting your home on the market? In my experience, buying a new unit could cost you over $10,000, and you don’t always get that investment back. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, one thing you could do is have a technician service the unit and then give you a written report that verifies the unit is operating correctly. Then once you sell your home, the inspector can show this report. &lt;strong&gt;Having it done in advance could save you thousands of dollars. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like me to take a look at your home and see where I can save you some money, feel free to call or email me anytime. I’d love to help in any way that I can!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-save-money-when-selling-your-home.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-save-money-when-selling-your-home.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Quick Update on the State of the Metro Richmond Market </title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/J0LgLe8KvlQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;What every buyer and seller should know about the Metro Richmond market.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are the latest numbers in Metro Richmond real estate? Today I’m sharing a few market indicators to keep you updated with the latest trends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s start with the average list price. Right now, we’re at $398,651, which is up 11.3% from this time last year. Meanwhile, new listings are down 11.5%. With these numbers, I believe &lt;strong&gt;percentages from the original list price to the adjusted sale price are so strong because of a lack of inventory.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Interest rates are starting to drop.%20http://localhost:4000/a-quick-update-on-the-state-of-the-metro-richmond-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Interest rates are starting to drop.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, let’s look at the market stats of the homes in different price ranges. Data from December 2022 versus January 2023 shows that everything’s trending about the same in terms of original list price, sold price, and adjusted sold price in homes priced from $0 to $350,000, with sellers no longer giving as many concessions and having to give up only 3% of the original list price. As for homes priced at $351,000 to $650,000, everything’s trending almost identically, with average days on market at 22. Lastly, homes priced at $651,000 and up are getting above asking price. Even with the concessions, they’re still selling at 102% of asking price with 27 days on the market. Again, I believe this is due to the lack of inventory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for some good news for buyers, interest rates are starting to drop, though they are still higher than what many people would prefer. However, &lt;strong&gt;when buying or selling a house, it is important to consider your lifestyle and current needs rather than just focusing on interest rates.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team is seeing homes go under contract within 7-8 days of being on the market, and closing for almost, if not above, asking price. If you’re a buyer or seller looking to learn more about the market in your neighborhood, call or email us. We can guide you through the process and share the good things happening in the Metro Richmond real estate market.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-quick-update-on-the-state-of-the-metro-richmond-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-quick-update-on-the-state-of-the-metro-richmond-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Home Upgrades That Will Get You a Good ROI</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bJW6jEdYcGY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Avoid making these home upgrades when prepping your home for the market.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently went on a listing appointment, and the number one question I got was: What do I need to do to get the most money when preparing my home for sale? In response to this, today I’m sharing what you need and don’t need to do to get top dollar for your property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The No. 1 issue that people are always concerned about is their roofs.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have a 20-year-old roof that is in good condition, replacing it will cost about $10,000. In my experience, you don’t necessarily need to replace it because when the house is sold, you’ll only get back your initial $10,000 investment. It will help sell the house, but it doesn’t bring you more money when you do sell it. This goes for windows, too, especially replacement windows, which are so expensive these days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, if you took that same $10,000 investment and used it to upgrade your kitchen or bathroom, you can get a $15,000 return. &lt;strong&gt;Not all replacements or upgrades will get you a good ROI.&lt;/strong&gt; If you are interested in knowing specifically what your house needs to get the most amount of money, feel free to call or email me. I’m always happy to help!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-home-upgrades-that-will-get-you-a-good-roi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-home-upgrades-that-will-get-you-a-good-roi.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
