<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Richmond Real Estate Podcast with Mark Adams</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Mark Adams & Associates - your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Mark Adams</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2023-06-21 15:05:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Mark Adams</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>office@markadamsteam.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Mark Adams</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Richmond Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Mark Adams & Associates - your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Truth About Our Housing Market Explained: Richmond’s June Housing Stats </title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-truth-about-our-housing-market-explained-richmond-s-june-housing-stats.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-05-30 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here’s what buyers and sellers need to know about our housing market. 

What’s going on in our housing market? Things are always changing, so today, I want to share the latest numbers you need to know for the June housing market in Richmond. Let’s delve into the details. 

The average sales price stands at nearly $404,000, indicating a slight increase compared to the same period last year. However, the number of new listings entering the market has decreased by 14.2%. To gain a broader perspective, I analyzed data dating back to 2006.

Remarkably, this month’s new listings mark the lowest count since 2006. As a result, homes are selling for a higher percentage of their asking prices. In the zero to $350,000 price range, properties are typically sold at 98% of the asking price. For homes priced between $351,000 and $650,000, the average sale price exceeds the asking price. And for properties priced at $651,000 and above, the average sale price is 103% above the asking price.

“The future of our market looks bright. ”

It is worth noting that we cannot predict when the market dynamics will shift and more inventory will become available. Currently, we are experiencing the lowest inventory since 2006. 

The truth is that no one knows for sure when or how our market will change, but it certainly will again. If you are thinking of buying or selling soon, just call or email us, and we’ll make sure to keep you informed on what’s happening in our market. We look forward to hearing from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s what buyers and sellers need to know about our housing market. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s what buyers and sellers need to know about our housing market. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Celebrating Our Pets and Community: Highlights From Our Recent Events</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/celebrating-our-pets-and-community-highlights-from-our-recent-pack-walk-event.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-05-24 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Sharing highlights from our recent events, which were fun and fulfilling.

Today, we’re very excited to share some of the highlights of our recent events. We had such a blast meeting new people and their dogs. Therefore, we wanted to take some time to share some of our favorite moments with you in the video above. 

We love to support local animal causes by organizing pack walks, pet food drives, and more. In April, we hosted a pack walk at Dogwood Dell, sponsored the Doggone 5K, 3K, and 1K events at the Pole Green Park, and supported the Richmond Animal League at the 2023 Woofstock event. Giving back to the community is an important part of our real estate service, and we love to be able to support our furry friends.

Enjoy these adorable doggie moments of our recent adventures in the video above—you might even recognize a face or two. Also, if you’re interested in entering the real estate market, remember that we’re here for you and that your support allows us to continue giving back to the community. Call or email us anytime, and we would be happy to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Sharing highlights from our recent events, which were fun and fulfilling.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Sharing highlights from our recent events, which were fun and fulfilling.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Real Estate Market Changes Daily: Stay Informed With Our May Update</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-real-estate-market-changes-daily-stay-informed-with-our-may-update.html</link>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-05-01 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

An important update on how much the real estate market is changing.

Today, we’re here with your May market update to help you stay informed so you can make smart real estate decisions. You need to be aware of certain changes, and we’re here with that information. 

First, the average sales price is up 10.5%, and new listings are down 13.7% from this time last year. Second, when looking at the sales-to-list-price ratio, we can see that it has stayed fairly consistent over the past few months in all price ranges, around 99%. However, things are very different currently, as many properties that have gone under contract in the last 30 days have sold well above the asking price. 

This shows that the real estate market changes daily, so it’s important to hire a Realtor who will keep you up to date. A lot of people don’t understand the current market because it’s changing so quickly, but we are here to help with that. 

“The market is changing rapidly.”

If you are thinking about selling, know that the decrease in new listings is driving prices up. Overall, just make sure to contact us because we can show you what’s going on in your specific neighborhood. Then if you want to buy a home, don’t get discouraged. There are still properties out there that are at a good price, and we can help you find them. 

If you have any questions about today’s market or need help buying or selling, don’t hesitate to reach out. You can call or email us anytime, and we would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>An important update on how much the real estate market is changing.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>An important update on how much the real estate market is changing.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Don't Let Your Dream Home Slip Away: How to Write an Offer That Stands Out</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/don-t-let-your-dream-home-slip-away-how-to-write-an-offer-that-stands-out.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-04-17 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

The secret to winning an offer comes down to these three tips.

If you’re in the market to buy a house, you know how challenging it can be to get your offer accepted. With the real estate market constantly changing, it can be hard to know how to write the best terms for the property you want to purchase. Today we’ll share three tips to help you write the best offer and increase your chances of getting it accepted.

First and foremost, it’s crucial to stay on top of the latest market data. This will help you determine the right offer price and terms for the specific area you’re interested in. At Mark Adams and Associates, we monitor the data every day, allowing us to provide our clients with informed advice on how to write the best offer for their chosen neighborhood.

Another important step is to have your agent call the listing agent before you write your offer. This will give you valuable insights into the seller’s preferences and the terms they’re looking for. By understanding what’s most important to the seller, you can tailor your offer accordingly, increasing your chances of getting it accepted.

“You can increase the chances of getting your offer accepted.”

Lastly, it’s essential to put all of the information you’ve gathered together to construct the best possible offer. By taking the market data and the seller’s preferences into account, you can create a competitive offer that stands out from the rest.

Remember, if you have any questions about this topic or real estate in general, please feel free to reach out to us by phone or email. We would be happy to help you with all of your real estate needs.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The secret to winning an offer comes down to these three tips.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The secret to winning an offer comes down to these three tips.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Discover the Latest Market Trends in Richmond</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/discover-the-latest-market-trends-in-richmond.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-03-31 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

An overview of the latest Metro Richmond housing market trends.

The real estate market is constantly changing, and staying up-to-date on the latest trends and statistics is crucial for buyers, sellers, and agents alike. To help you do this, we’re taking a closer look at the current real estate market in Metro Richmond and sharing some important data that can help you make informed decisions. 

First, the average sales price in Metro Richmond for March is $400,748. This is up by 7.4% from the previous year. However, the number of new listings from the same time last year is down by 12.7%, with only 24,262 new listings. 

Properties priced from $1 to $350,000 had an average sales price of $252,000 and sellers received an average of $6,000 in concessions, which brought the adjusted sold price to $243,000, or 96% of the original asking price. Also, the properties stayed on the market for an average of 24 days.

“It’s essential to work with an agent who understands the current market trends.”

For properties priced between 351,000 and 650,000, the numbers have remained relatively consistent throughout the year. They’re selling at around 99% of their asking price, with the occasional sale at 98% or 100%. Then for properties priced at 651,000 and above, the market is still strong, with some homes selling above the asking price. 

The market trends for lower-priced properties suggest that some agents are not doing their due diligence when it comes to researching the market. There have been multiple offers on properties in the last 30 days, but some agents are making offers above the asking price without finding out if there are any other offers on the table. This lack of research and education is leading to clients being confused and missing opportunities. 

If you want to buy or sell a property in Richmond, it’s essential to work with an agent who understands the current market trends and can educate you on what’s happening in your neck of the woods. If you want help with this or want to know exactly how much your house is worth, give us a call and we’ll share this data with you. We look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>An overview of the latest Metro Richmond housing market trends.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>An overview of the latest Metro Richmond housing market trends.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Renovate Your Home Without Breaking the Bank</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/renovate-your-home-without-breaking-the-bank.html</link>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-03-23 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Our partners can help you renovate your home with minimal stress.

Today, I have some exciting news to share with you! Lately, I’ve been frequently getting asked if renovating the entire house is necessary for selling in the current real estate market. The short answer is that it depends on the location, but I recommend making your house look as nice as possible to get a higher price and sell it faster. In some cases, a full renovation is necessary to get a better return on your investment.

The good news is that we’ve partnered with a few companies that can do these three things for you: loan you the money, hire the contractors, and manage the project. Plus, they won’t charge you a fee, they just have you pay them back when the house sells. It’s a win-win situation! 

If you’re interested, call or email me anytime. I’d be happy to come out and see if this service is right for you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our partners can help you renovate your home with minimal stress.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our partners can help you renovate your home with minimal stress.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Sellers Need To Know About Today’s Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-sellers-need-to-know-about-today-s-market.html</link>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-03-06 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Changes in home prices affect properties in all price ranges.

I am excited to share the March edition of the Metro Richmond Real Estate Market Quick Stats with you today. In the last 30 days, the average sales price and the number of new listings have changed, affecting homes in all price ranges, so I am here to keep you up to date. 

First, the average sales price is $351,239, up 6.1% from last year. Secondly, the number of new listings is around 1,399, down 26.8% from last year. This affects all homes differently, so I have split properties into three price ranges. 

In the $0 to $350,000 price range, the average house came onto the market at $271,500, sold for $261,500, and included $5,050 of concessions. That means the adjusted sold price is $256,450, and the list-to-sold-price ratio is 94%. Lastly, these homes stayed on the market for an average of 24 days. 

“The most opportunity is in the lower price range.”

We know that values aren’t going down, so these stats show us that sellers are contributing more and more to the buyers’ costs. However, this isn’t the same in every price range—in the $351,000 to $650,000 price range, the list-to-sold-price ratio is 98%, and in the $651,000 and up price range, the ratio is 101%. Plus, the numbers have stayed very similar over the last few months in these two ranges, while it has changed more in the first price range. 

Typically, when you have a lack of inventory, as we do, that keeps the prices higher. This shows more in the two higher price ranges, while there is the most opportunity in the lower one. Since sellers know they’re going to have to compromise to sell their houses, buyers will have more opportunities. 

If your house is in the lower price range and you’re considering selling, I recommend getting your home on the market sooner rather than later. Act before the list-to-sold-price ratio continues to drop. If your house is in one of the higher price ranges, you’ll get close to asking price, if not more, so you have more time. 

If you want to know what your property is worth and what a buyer might pay for it, call me anytime! I would be happy to look at the numbers in your neighborhood and share that information with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Changes in home prices affect properties in all price ranges.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Changes in home prices affect properties in all price ranges.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How To Save Money When Selling Your Home</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-save-money-when-selling-your-home.html</link>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-02-21 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Having your HVAC serviced could save you thousands of dollars.

Do you have an older air conditioning unit and are debating whether or not to replace it before putting your home on the market? In my experience, buying a new unit could cost you over $10,000, and you don’t always get that investment back. 

However, one thing you could do is have a technician service the unit and then give you a written report that verifies the unit is operating correctly. Then once you sell your home, the inspector can show this report. Having it done in advance could save you thousands of dollars. 

If you would like me to take a look at your home and see where I can save you some money, feel free to call or email me anytime. I’d love to help in any way that I can!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Having your HVAC serviced could save you thousands of dollars.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Having your HVAC serviced could save you thousands of dollars.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Quick Update on the State of the Metro Richmond Market </title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-quick-update-on-the-state-of-the-metro-richmond-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-02-09 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What every buyer and seller should know about the Metro Richmond market.

What are the latest numbers in Metro Richmond real estate? Today I’m sharing a few market indicators to keep you updated with the latest trends.

Let’s start with the average list price. Right now, we’re at $398,651, which is up 11.3% from this time last year. Meanwhile, new listings are down 11.5%. With these numbers, I believe percentages from the original list price to the adjusted sale price are so strong because of a lack of inventory.

“Interest rates are starting to drop.”

Next, let’s look at the market stats of the homes in different price ranges. Data from December 2022 versus January 2023 shows that everything’s trending about the same in terms of original list price, sold price, and adjusted sold price in homes priced from $0 to $350,000, with sellers no longer giving as many concessions and having to give up only 3% of the original list price. As for homes priced at $351,000 to $650,000, everything’s trending almost identically, with average days on market at 22. Lastly, homes priced at $651,000 and up are getting above asking price. Even with the concessions, they’re still selling at 102% of asking price with 27 days on the market. Again, I believe this is due to the lack of inventory.

As for some good news for buyers, interest rates are starting to drop, though they are still higher than what many people would prefer. However, when buying or selling a house, it is important to consider your lifestyle and current needs rather than just focusing on interest rates.

Our team is seeing homes go under contract within 7-8 days of being on the market, and closing for almost, if not above, asking price. If you’re a buyer or seller looking to learn more about the market in your neighborhood, call or email us. We can guide you through the process and share the good things happening in the Metro Richmond real estate market.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What every buyer and seller should know about the Metro Richmond market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What every buyer and seller should know about the Metro Richmond market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Home Upgrades That Will Get You a Good ROI</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-home-upgrades-that-will-get-you-a-good-roi.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-01-23 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Avoid making these home upgrades when prepping your home for the market.

I recently went on a listing appointment, and the number one question I got was: What do I need to do to get the most money when preparing my home for sale? In response to this, today I’m sharing what you need and don’t need to do to get top dollar for your property.

The No. 1 issue that people are always concerned about is their roofs. If you have a 20-year-old roof that is in good condition, replacing it will cost about $10,000. In my experience, you don’t necessarily need to replace it because when the house is sold, you’ll only get back your initial $10,000 investment. It will help sell the house, but it doesn’t bring you more money when you do sell it. This goes for windows, too, especially replacement windows, which are so expensive these days. 

However, if you took that same $10,000 investment and used it to upgrade your kitchen or bathroom, you can get a $15,000 return. Not all replacements or upgrades will get you a good ROI. If you are interested in knowing specifically what your house needs to get the most amount of money, feel free to call or email me. I’m always happy to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Avoid making these home upgrades when prepping your home for the market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Avoid making these home upgrades when prepping your home for the market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Buyers and Sellers Should Know About Our Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-buyers-and-sellers-should-know-about-our-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2023-01-06 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here’s a quick housing market update for the beginning of 2023. 

Happy New Year! I am so excited for 2023, and as usual, I wanted to show you exactly what’s going on in our Metro Richmond real estate market. 

First, the average original list price for all the homes that were sold in the last 30 days was $387,000, and the average sold price for these properties was $388,000. That being said, the average seller offered $4,700 in concessions, meaning the adjusted sale price after you subtract the concessions is $383,300, or 99% of the original asking price. Meanwhile, the average home is spending 18 days on the market. 

“Buyers shouldn’t wait to make a move.”

This means that sellers are giving buyers concessions to keep their offers high, and it seems to be working. At the same time, inventory is decreasing. There were 2,713 homes available in November, but there were only 2,127 in December. 

If you’re thinking about selling your house, we’re on the cusp of the spring market, which will have low inventory, good sales prices, and more benefits for sellers. Buyers shouldn’t wait to make a move. Supply is scarce, and the longer you wait, the more competition you’ll have. 

If you’re thinking about buying or selling, you need to meet with me. Just give me a call or send me an email; I’d love to speak with you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s a quick housing market update for the beginning of 2023. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s a quick housing market update for the beginning of 2023. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>An Important Market Update for December</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-important-market-update-for-december.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-12-09 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

How interest rates have changed the market in favor of first-time buyers.

Today I am excited to share another important market update with you all! Can you believe it is already December? As most of you know, I love to share the market data so you can see for yourselves what’s going on in the MLS. That way you can make an informed decision on what’s best for you and your family. 

Let’s start with the average sales price. It is currently $395,625, which is 9.2% higher than it was last year. Property values have risen, which is great news for homeowners. As prices fluctuate, it is important to look into how much sellers are compromising with their buyers, as this greatly affects the state of the market.

“Sellers are working with buyers much more in the lower price range that is typically for first-time buyers.”

To figure this out, I made a table comparing the adjusted sold prices in three different price ranges. The ranges are zero to $350,000, $351,000 to $650,000, and $651,000 and up. You can look at which price range you fall in to know the specific information that pertains to you. To figure out the adjusted sold price percentages, I compared the original list price to the sold price and accounted for concessions. 

In the first price range, the adjusted sold price percentage is 95%, with 18 days on market. In the second price range, it’s 99%, with 21 days on market. The third price range is 100.4%, with 25 days on market. Overall, the important thing I take from this data is that sellers are working with buyers much more in the lower price range that is typically for first-time buyers. 

I believe the reason for this is that interest rates are so high. Sellers are contributing more to buyers to help them lower their rates so they can start with a more manageable mortgage payment. This is great news for first-time homebuyers. 

If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out. Also, I would love to help you do a comparative market analysis for your specific area to find out the value of your home. Call or email me anytime, and I would love to hear from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How interest rates have changed the market in favor of first-time buyers.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How interest rates have changed the market in favor of first-time buyers.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Highlights: Client Appreciation Day at the Zoo</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/highlights-client-appreciation-day-at-the-zoo.html</link>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-11-23 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

A few highlights from our 6th annual Client Appreciation Day at the zoo!

We recently had our 6th annual Client Appreciation Day at the Zoo and were thrilled to see all of you there. Not only was this a day to show gratitude to our clients for their support over the years, but it was also an opportunity to support our local community. We gathered pet food donations to support Feed More’s Meals on Wheels program, which helps seniors and their animal companions.

We hope you enjoyed the event as much as we did, and we look forward to seeing you next year! Remember, if you have any real estate needs or questions, don’t hesitate to reach out through phone call or email. We’d be delighted to help you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>A few highlights from our 6th annual Client Appreciation Day at the zoo!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>A few highlights from our 6th annual Client Appreciation Day at the zoo!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What’s Really Happening in Our Housing Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-really-happening-in-our-housing-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-11-03 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What buyers and sellers need to know about our local housing market. 

Today, I’m bringing you the monthly market update so you can see exactly what’s going on. If you look at the average sales price at 0:13 in the video, you can see that the average sales price is $402,517. This number is still up 12% over this time last year. That means that home values are staying really strong right now.

The next statistic I like to look at is days on market. In September, it was eight days, and in October, it was also eight days. The average days on market is slowly creeping up, but it’s still really low.

Next, let’s look at the list-to-sales-price ratio. That gives us an idea of how much negotiating goes along with purchasing a house. In September, it was a little over 100%. In October, it was very similar, so homes are still selling at high prices.

“Rate buydowns are a great option for today’s buyers. ”

Sellers are still doing very well in this market. So that begs the question: How about the buyers? Everybody knows that the interest rate is up to 7%. However, one thing I love about this country is that anytime we’re in a situation like this, people in the industry figure out solutions.

Right now, buyers can opt for a buydown, where you pay money upfront to lower your interest rate. Another thing we’re seeing, which I haven’t seen since I got in the business 23 years ago, is assumable mortgages. With these, you can take on a seller’s current mortgage and their lower interest rate. 

If you’d like some specific home-buying advice or have any other questions, please call or email me. I am always willing to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What buyers and sellers need to know about our local housing market. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What buyers and sellers need to know about our local housing market. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Do These 3 Things Before You Buy</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/do-these-3-things-before-you-buy.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-10-13 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

You shouldn’t purchase a house unless you have done these three things.

Are you thinking about buying a house right now? You definitely should not buy a house until you do these three things:

1. Make a list of the non-negotiables you want in the house. There’s no such thing as the perfect house, so you want to have a list of your non-negotiables. When Lisa and I searched for our current house, we each made a list of ten, and then combined them into a single list of ten. That’s how we chose this house. We knew when we looked at it that it was exactly what we were looking for because we had a list.

“Make decisions based on logic, not emotion.”

2. Create a budget. How much do you want to spend? Take that information, go to a trusted loan officer mortgage company, and find out what the terms are for getting a mortgage.

3. Make a plan. What is it that you’re specifically looking for in the house, location, and price? I often see buyers making decisions based on emotions and not logic. If you have a list and a budget, then ask yourself if this is the house that you want to buy. Does it meet your criteria? Is this the location that you want to be in, and is this the price you want to pay?

When houses were bid $20,000 above asking price, that was based on emotion and not logic. There’s nothing wrong with paying more for a house as long as you’re making a logical decision. Lisa and I bought our house for $22,000 over asking price because it met all of our criteria.

If you have any questions or want help with the process, reach out to me by phone or email. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>You shouldn’t purchase a house unless you have done these three things.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>You shouldn’t purchase a house unless you have done these three things.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>We Are Sending You Homebot for Free!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/we-are-sending-you-homebot-for-free.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-10-03 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+Sending+You+Homebot+for+Free!.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We&rsquo;re sending you the Homebot app, so here are some of its great features.

&nbsp;

Do you want to know what your home is worth? Do you want to know how much equity you have in your house? I can provide those answers for free right now. For years, my team and I have been researching companies for an app that we could send to our clients for free that would tell them the value of their homes. We finally found it, and it’s called Homebot. 

Here are a few of its great features: 

1. Home value. One tap shows you the value of your home. The app may not know about your home’s amenities, so you can also adjust the value higher or lower based on what your home includes. 

2. Your equity position. By the time the average American retires, 83% of their wealth comes from home equity. Homebot helps you keep track of your equity position.

3. Amortization chart. This tells you how much you would save on interest if you made extra mortgage payments. Personalized calculations can help you save money and pay off your loans quicker. 

“This app has so many cool features that we think you’ll enjoy exploring.”

4. Rent estimation. If you’ve considered renting out your house or making it an Airbnb, the app will tell you how much you can charge for it. 

This app has so many cool features that we think you’ll enjoy exploring. They also have a feature where you can tap a button if you want more specific information about that part of the app. They even have features that can help if you’re thinking about buying a property.

Your house is the largest asset you’re ever likely to own, and Homebot can help you make informed decisions. It provides valuable market data and wealth-building insights. Homebot is free to you, and it’s coming to your email from us, so be on the lookout for it.

Enter your address here for your instant home value.

If you have questions for us about real estate or if we can help you in any way, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone, text, or email. We would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+Sending+You+Homebot+for+Free!.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+Sending+You+Homebot+for+Free!.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’re sending you the Homebot app, so here are some of its great features.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’re sending you the Homebot app, so here are some of its great features.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Exactly Is Happening in Our Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-exactly-is-happening-in-our-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-09-21 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here’s what you need to know about our latest housing market numbers. 

“What’s really going on in the real estate market?” I receive this question nearly every day. Today I’ll share all the relevant market data you need to know.

I always like to start things with the average sales price. In June 2022, the average price was $418,000, but in August, it was $402,000. Does this mean you should be worried about a housing market crash? In my opinion, no. The average sales price is still up 10.2% year over year. Our market is certainly changing, but it won’t crash.

“Buyers are comfortable with current interest rates and still want to get into homes.”

For another sign that our market is changing, let’s look at the average days on market. The average home sold in 13 days in June and 16 in August. Our market is slowing down, but not dramatically. 

Meanwhile, the list-to-sales-price ratio was 105% in May and fell to 101% in August. Sellers are still receiving over their asking prices, but the trend is moving down. 

What does all this mean for the future of our market? I believe the initial shock of higher interest rates stalled our market. People didn’t know what was happening, so they stayed put until they could wrap their heads around the situation. However, I believe this period is now over or almost over. Buyers are comfortable with current interest rates and still want to get into homes. Plus, more inventory means buyers have more options, so many who sat out during the crazy pandemic market may look for houses once again. 

This is still a good market for both buyers and sellers. If you have questions about this topic or anything else, please call or email me. I look forward to hearing from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s what you need to know about our latest housing market numbers. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s what you need to know about our latest housing market numbers. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What You Should and Shouldn’t Do When Buying </title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-you-should-and-shouldnt-do-when-buying.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-09-01 11:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Three tips that you should know for a stress-free home buying experience. 

Purchasing a home involves a lot of processes that can be overwhelming. If you want your home-buying journey to be as smooth as possible, here are a few tips to keep in mind:

1. Don’t quit your day job. Most banks want to see your history of employment, so don’t quit your job while in the process of buying a home. Also, if you have open credit card accounts, make sure you don’t make unusually expensive purchases or close an account unless it has been approved by your loan officer. 

2. Pay your bills on time. Having a history of paying your bills on time will look good on your record. 

3. Get pre-qualified. One of the best things you can do when buying a home is to reach out to a loan officer who can check your credit. 

If you have more questions about this topic or need help with your buying plans, call or email me. I want to be your real estate consultant!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Three tips that you should know for a stress-free home buying experience. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Three tips that you should know for a stress-free home buying experience. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Don’t Hire an Agent Before Doing This</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dont-hire-an-agent-before-doing-this.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-08-15 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Three questions you need to ask a real estate agent before hiring them. 

How can you pick the right real estate agent? Helping you buy or sell a home is a crucial role, so it’s important to pick the best person for the job. Today we’re sharing three questions you should ask agents when interviewing them:

 1. How long have they been in the business? We recommend you hire agents with at least five years of experience. Remember, whether you hire someone who’s been in the business for 30 minutes or 30 years, you’ll still be paying them the same fee. 

2. How many homes have they sold in your area? Not only should your agent know your region, but they should also know what’s been happening recently. That’s why we recommend you work with someone who has sold at least three to five homes in the last month. This way, you can be sure they have their finger on the pulse of your market. 

 

“Whether you hire someone who has been in the business for 30 minutes or 30 years, you’ll still be paying them the same fee. ”

 

3. What is their list-to-sales price ratio? If you don’t know, this ratio measures what percentage of the asking price an agent’s clients receive on average. If an agent consistently sells homes for exactly what their list prices are, their list-to-sales price ratio will be 100%. You should be able to ask your agent or look up the average ratio in your area. Once you find it out, compare their ratio to the average. We recommend you work with agents whose ratio is above the average for your area. 

Bonus Question: Ask for three or four references from the buyer or seller side. Call their past clients and see if they are happy with the service they received.

If you would like to ask us these questions or have other concerns, please call or email us. We are always willing to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Three questions you need to ask a real estate agent before hiring them. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Three questions you need to ask a real estate agent before hiring them. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Market is Shifting - So Can We</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/is-our-market-crashing-or-slowing-down.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-07-29 10:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here’s what you need to know about our changing housing market.

The latest numbers are in—what do they say about our housing market? Conditions are changing, so if you aren’t informed, you could make huge decisions based on outdated information. Today we’ll share everything you need to know about our market. 

Our average sales price is currently $419,384, which is up 14.5% year over year. Meanwhile, the average home is selling for 105% of its list price. That seems high, and it is, but this number is lower than it has been in the last few months. In June, the average list-to-sales price ratio was 105.4%, and in April, it was 106.1%. The market certainly isn’t crashing, but it’s slowing down. 

“Rising interest rates are causing our market to shift. ”

As of the day we’re writing this blog, our market had 229 price reductions. Each reduction was around 5.74% on average. That tells us that our market is changing, and the biggest reason for this shift is our rising interest rates. As rates increase, buyers’ purchasing power decreases. 

We don’t know for sure where our market is heading. However, we don’t predict a crash. Instead, it’s more likely that our market will slow down and eventually stabilize. 

If you have questions about today’s topic or anything else, please call or email us. We are always willing to help! 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s what you need to know about our changing housing market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s what you need to know about our changing housing market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Are We Responding to Inflation?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-are-we-responding-to-inflation.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-07-06 16:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Inflation is affecting affordability, so we’re offering more for less. 

Our market is shifting. Inflation is up, and it’s affecting both buyers and sellers. We want to get ahead of this issue, so we decided we need to provide more value to our sellers while reducing our costs. Let us explain.

It’s easy to forget now, but before the real estate crash of 2008, 2005 and 2006 were the best years for real estate sales in history. We’ve been around long enough to remember this time, and many agents became complacent with their marketing and other services. We believe a lot of agents today have become complacent in a similar way since the market has been so great for so long. 

We’ve never believed in being complacent, so we’re doing a few things to make sure our services are the best they can be. First, we’re introducing variable rate commissions to help with costs. Plus, we’re improving our professional photography to include traditional and drone photos. Your agent won’t be awkwardly taking photos of your property with their iPhone if you work with us. We’ll even give you the pictures once you close. After all, your home rarely looks better than when you’re trying to sell. 

“No matter what your needs are, we have you covered.”

We also have a full-time marketing coordinator to get your home in front of as many buyers as possible. She’ll market your home to over 40 high-traffic websites so everyone can see your property. We’re also introducing an easy-exit release, so if you feel like we aren’t doing what we promised we would, you can walk away with no strings attached. 

What if you don’t want to list your home on the open market? Don’t worry; we also have an express offers program. We can get you an all-cash offer on your home within 24 hours. If you want to sell the easy way, this option might be for you. 

These are just some of the things we offer our clients. If you have questions about today’s topic or anything else, please call or email us. We are always willing to help! 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Inflation is affecting affordability, so we’re offering more for less. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Inflation is affecting affordability, so we’re offering more for less. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Mark Adams Story</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-mark-adams-story.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-06-22 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here’s the story of how I got into the real estate business.

I love building things and working with people. Looking back, it’s not surprising that I ended up building my own company where a large part of daily operations include working with people and doing what I love. 

When I was growing up, my parents built several commercial buildings and owned several businesses at the same time. They would always include me and my siblings in the construction process and the business side of things. They made it fun, and it never really felt like work. Looking back, I’m pretty sure that’s where I got my entrepreneurial spirit. 

One of the best things my dad taught all of us was, “There’s nothing you can’t do if you put your mind to it.” When I was 22, Lisa and I moved to Virginia and the first thing my parents told me to do was buy a house and start building equity for the future. They also suggested building a house because of their experience in construction, and the next thing you know, we found a lot and started building the house.

“We take great pride in the relationships we build.”

We hired a jack leg carpenter, Harold Yoho, who helped us along with my dad, working seven days a week for three months to build that house. We got to the closing table, I was fussing about some bills, and the attorney told me that I had made $20,000 in three months by building the house. I knew then that I was going to be in real estate. Since then, Lisa and I have built three houses together and renovated a fourth. 

We started our real estate company in 1999 with the same drive, determination, and work ethic that we learned from building all those houses. Buying or selling a home is typically the single biggest investment people make. We understand how important that is and how stressful that process can be. That’s why our team consists of a full-time client care manager, a full-time marketing manager, and full-time Realtors with decades of experience so all of your needs are taken care of. We take great pride in the relationships we build and always work relentlessly on our clients’ behalf to help them achieve their real estate goals.

If you have any real estate goals you’d like to discuss or just any general questions, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s the story of how I got into the real estate business.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s the story of how I got into the real estate business.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Important Tools for Today’s Buyers and Sellers</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-important-tools-for-todays-homebuyers.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-05-29 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/3+Important+Tools+for+Today%E2%80%99s+Buyers+and+Sellers.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here are three tools you can use to better compete in today’s market.

The No. 1 question that we’ve been getting from buyers lately is, “How do we navigate this changing market?” I’ve been in the real estate industry for 23 years now, and I’ve sold homes in both up and down markets. That uniquely qualifies me to help our clients through this change in season. Here are three tools that will help buyers successfully secure a home, even if they also have one they need to sell:

1. Home equity lines of credit (HELOCs). This loan allows you to take up to 80% of the equity in your current home and use it as a down payment on your next house. With a HELOC, you can buy your second house without it being contingent on the sale of your first home, which can be a massive liability for buyers in today’s market.

2. Adjustable rate mortgages (ARMs). The introductory rate for an ARM is typically less than the interest rate on a fixed mortgage. It will go up over time, but it allows you to start low. Interest rates have increased recently, so this option is becoming more popular.

“A HELOC lets you take up to 80% of the equity in your current home to use as a down payment on your next house.”

3. The bank can purchase the house on your behalf. Many buyers are competing with cash in this market. Realizing this, many banks will purchase your next home for you and sell it back to you if you qualify. For this program, you will need to pay 3% of the home’s purchase price, but that’s still relatively inexpensive considering how much you might pay by competing in the traditional market.

I constantly search for ways to give my clients the best chance of competing in this marketplace, so if you have any questions about these tools or would like to explore other options, give me a call or send me an email. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/3+Important+Tools+for+Today%E2%80%99s+Buyers+and+Sellers.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/3+Important+Tools+for+Today%E2%80%99s+Buyers+and+Sellers.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are three tools you can use to better compete in today’s market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are three tools you can use to better compete in today’s market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Project Green and Their Green Mosquito Control</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/project-green-and-their-green-mosquito-control.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-05-14 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Project+Green+and+Their+Green+Mosquito+Control+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

How Project Green can help control your mosquitoes organically.

If you’ve got mosquitoes, Alex Kepner from Project Green has an organic cure. Years ago, Lisa got into organic gardening, and she learned just how important the environment is and how much we rely on bees. We get a ton of mosquitoes in our backyard, and Lisa’s research led us to Project Green and their organic mosquito control. We brought Alex out here today to share a bit about what he does. 

How is your treatment different?

Our goal is to control mosquitoes, fleas, and ticks with natural products like cedar and peppermint oils. At the same time, we don’t want to target the pollinators and beneficial insects like bees and ladybugs. 

What does it look like when you treat our yard, and how is it different from your competitors?

We use a fogging backpack blower to fog the entire yard and create a perimeter. We’ll target areas where there’s a buildup of mosquitoes, like debris piles, gutters, etc. The methods aren’t much different from what other companies do. The big difference is what’s in the tank.

“Their goal is to control mosquitoes organically while leaving the pollinators unharmed.”

You mention that it kills fleas and ticks. We have a dog who likes to eat grass, so is the treatment safe for pets?

Fortunately, it’s safe for dogs, and we understand that pet safety is a big priority for homeowners. It’s such a fine mist, and it’s made up of essential oils and chemicals that are found in household products. There is little to no harm to dogs. The FDA says there is zero toxicity in our products. 

How long does the treatment last?

We spray on three-week cycles, but we can run into some issues with heavy rains diluting the product. We ask homeowners to work with us on this. If you see standing water or piles of debris, eliminate them so that we can get the best result.

Sounds like the only thing left to do is get my neighbors on board so that we’re all using the same organic solution. If you want to have Alex take a look at your yard, call him at 804-299-5322 or email him at hello@projectgreenva.com. Of course, if you have any real estate questions, feel free to call or email us as well. We’d love to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Project+Green+and+Their+Green+Mosquito+Control+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Project+Green+and+Their+Green+Mosquito+Control+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How Project Green can help control your mosquitoes organically.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How Project Green can help control your mosquitoes organically.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Thanks for Supporting Feed More</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/recapping-panera-pups-and-prizes.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-05-08 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Thanks+for+Supporting+Feed+More+(2).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s a look at the great time we had at our recent community event.

We want to thank everyone who donated to our event, both in person or virtually. This is our 14th year collecting donations for Feed More, and this year we collected a whole truckload of pet food donations for their pet food pantry. This goes toward helping provide senior citizens and shut-ins with food for their pets.

This cause is so important because oftentimes they worry about having to give up their companion, or choose between picking up the prescriptions/food for the animal. Many seniors are often isolated, so keeping a companion in their home is truly a gift. We are very grateful for everyone who chooses to do business with our team because they allow us the opportunity to give back to our community.

Thank you again for spending the morning with us, and letting us love on your precious pups. We can’t wait to tell you how much we raised for local pets in need in a future video. 

Today we’re sharing a quick slideshow of some great moments that we captured throughout the event. Watch the video above to see it all.

If you have any questions for me about real estate, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Thanks+for+Supporting+Feed+More+(2).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Thanks+for+Supporting+Feed+More+(2).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s a look at the great time we had at our recent community event.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s a look at the great time we had at our recent community event.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Your April 2022 Virginia Housing Market Update</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/your-april-2022-virginia-housing-market-update.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-04-26 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/WW91ciBBcHJpbCAyMDIyIFZpcmdpbmlhIEhvdXNpbmcgTWFya2V0IFVwZGF0ZS5tcDQ%3D+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s the latest data from our local Central Virginia real estate market.

Are you interested in knowing where home prices are going? Today we want to go over the market data from April and give you an idea of where our market is headed. You’ll get a chance to see the same numbers that the economists see.

You can watch the full video above, or skip to each section using the timestamps provided:

0:00 — Introducing today’s topic

0:34 — The average and median sales price 

1:25 — The number of new listings

2:45 — Our closed sales and list-to-sales-price ratio

3:36 — The national historical median home value

4:50 — The market usually rises and levels off, but 2020 was not normal

5:56 — We’re looking at some sort of market adjustment

7:10 — Wrapping up

If you have any questions about these stats or real estate in general, feel free to call or email us. We would love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/WW91ciBBcHJpbCAyMDIyIFZpcmdpbmlhIEhvdXNpbmcgTWFya2V0IFVwZGF0ZS5tcDQ%3D+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/WW91ciBBcHJpbCAyMDIyIFZpcmdpbmlhIEhvdXNpbmcgTWFya2V0IFVwZGF0ZS5tcDQ%3D+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s the latest data from our local Central Virginia real estate market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s the latest data from our local Central Virginia real estate market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Announcing Our Panera, Pups, & Prizes Event</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/announcing-our-panera-pups-prizes-event.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-04-10 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Announcing+Our+Panera%2C+Pups%2C+%26+Prizes+Event.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We’re hosting a Panera, Pups, and Prizes event on April 30 at 9 a.m.

We’ve got a big announcement for you! We’re hosting an event we call Panera, Pups, and Prizes.

It’s an opportunity to say thank you to our clients, but we’re also going to do a pet food drive for Feed More and Meals on Wheels. About 10 years ago, we saw a story about how the people these food drive programs serve often have pets. Many of them had to give up their pets because they didn’t have enough food for them. Ever since we saw that, we’ve been donating pet food, and there’s a big need out there for it. Please bring some pet food with you if you can!

“We want to meet your dog!”

The bottom line is that we see your posts all the time, and we want to meet both you and your pup in person. To do that, we’re willing to bribe you with a free Panera breakfast. We’re also going to have a doggy treasure hunt, where you and your pup can look for these little ice cream cones with treats inside. Every pup that shows up will get a little doggy bag, and we have $500 worth of prizes that you can win. The first-place reward is $100! To sign-up for this event and have a chance to win the grand prize, click here.

Please join us at 7521 Comanche Drive on April 30 from 9 a.m. to 11 a.m. We’d love to see you there. If you have any questions in the meantime, feel free to call or email us. We’d love to hear from you.


</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Announcing+Our+Panera%2C+Pups%2C+%26+Prizes+Event.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Announcing+Our+Panera%2C+Pups%2C+%26+Prizes+Event.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’re hosting a Panera, Pups, and Prizes event on April 30 at 9 a.m.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’re hosting a Panera, Pups, and Prizes event on April 30 at 9 a.m.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>March Update for Richmond Real Estate</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/march-update-for-richmond-real-estate.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-03-27 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/March+Update+for+Richmond+Real+Estate.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s a breakdown of the latest monthly numbers for Richmond real estate.

If interest rates go up, how does that affect you? In the last month, interest rates have gone up almost a full 1%. We’ll talk about how that affects both buyers and sellers, but first, I want to share some important market statistics with you from February:


  
    The median sale price is up from $301,000 to $329,000 year over year. That’s an 8.5% increase.
  
  
    The average sale price is up from $332,089 to $361,141. That’s nearly an 8% increase.
  
  
    New listings are up slightly from 1,795 to 1,907 year over year. That’s a good sign.
  
  
    Closed sales are down from 1,475 to 1,314 year over year. The reason for this is twofold. Inventory is obviously putting a constraint on things, but a lot more buyers are backing out of contracts these days because they’re having to make such crazy, competitive offers to win.
  
  
    The average days on market remains flat at around six days.
  
  
    The list-to-sale price ratio for the average home is up from 100.9% to 102%. This tells us houses are selling for more.
  


“We’ve seen 120 months of consecutive year-over-year price gains.”

The largest sector of people buying homes these days are first-time homebuyers. If interest rates go up, it’s going to push some of them out of the market, and that may cause inventory to spike. I don’t know when it’s going to happen, but the market is going to have to adjust. 

Another stat I read said that we’ve seen 120 months of consecutive year-over-year price gains. That’s 10 years in a row of appreciation on a monthly basis. There has to be some sort of adjustment coming; we just don’t know when it’s going to happen.

I encourage buyers out there not to give up. There are still properties out there. For sellers, if you look at the numbers, you will see that now is an opportune time to list before the market inevitably shifts. 

If you’re interested in buying, selling, or both, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email today with any questions you might have. We would love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/March+Update+for+Richmond+Real+Estate.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/March+Update+for+Richmond+Real+Estate.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s a breakdown of the latest monthly numbers for Richmond real estate.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s a breakdown of the latest monthly numbers for Richmond real estate.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Inspect Your Fire Extinguishers</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/inspect-your-fire-extinguishers.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-03-07 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.

Today I want to talk about fire extinguisher safety and inspections. When I was doing my research on this topic, the first thing I did was look at my fire extinguishers to see if they were safe, full, and able to be used correctly. As it turns out, mine weren’t. Do you remember the last time you checked yours? I have a few helpful tips I learned that I wanted to share with you. 

First, when you store your fire extinguisher, the information needs to face the outside so the user can see it when they’re grabbing the canister. You’ll also notice a little safety pin on the top - this is what keeps you from accidentally depressing the fire extinguisher. There’s also a gauge that shows how full your extinguisher is. Now keep in mind, just because the canister is full, that doesn’t mean the extinguisher is still effective. They do have expiration dates.

Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years and exchanged for a new one. I did some shopping online, and I found that they are usually between $20 to $30 and can even be bought in packages. Some now come in a smaller form that is perfect to keep in the kitchen. The smaller ones are about the size of an aerosol can, and they’re designed to spray a small fire on your cooktop, but a larger one should still be kept close by.

“Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years.”

Did you know there are three classes of fire extinguishers? Class A is for wood or paper products, class B is for liquids, and class C is for electrical fires. When you’re buying your fire extinguisher, you want to get an A, B, and C class fire extinguisher for your kitchen. If you like candles or have a fireplace in the house you should have another fire extinguisher nearby.

I hope you found this information valuable. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me by phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Inspect Your Fire Extinguishers</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/fire-extinguisher-safety-and-inspections.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-03-07 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.

Today I’ll talk about fire extinguisher safety and inspections. When I was doing my research on this topic, the first thing I did was look at my fire extinguishers to see if they were safe, full, and able to be used correctly. I discovered that mine weren’t.

I learned that when you store your fire extinguisher, the information needs to face the outside so the user can see it when they’re grabbing the canister. The little safety pin keeps from you accidentally depressing the fire extinguisher. There’s also a gauge that shows how full your extinguisher is.

Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years and exchanged for a new one. They are usually between $20 to $30 and can even be bought in packages. Some now come in a smaller form that is perfect to keep in the kitchen. The smaller ones are about the size of an aerosol can, and they’re designed to spray a small fire on your cooktop, but a larger one should still be close by.

“Fire extinguishers should be thrown out after about 12 to 13 years.”

There are three classes of fire extinguishers; Class A is for wood or paper products, class B is for liquids, and class C is for electrical fires. When you’re buying your fire extinguisher, you want to get an A, B, and C class fire extinguisher for your kitchen. If you like candles or have a fireplace in the house you should have another fire extinguisher nearby.

I hope you found this information valuable. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me by phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I did some research on fire extinguishers and want to share what I learned.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Sellers and Buyers Can Navigate Our Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-sellers-and-buyers-can-navigate-our-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-02-21 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/How+Sellers+and+Buyers+Can+Navigate+Our+Market+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Comparing today’s market to January 2021 and what the numbers mean for you.

Do you want to know what’s going on in real estate? Today we’ll be looking at data from Central Virginia’s MLS, which covers single-family homes, townhouses, and condos. I’ll mostly be comparing data from 2021 to 2022 so that we can see how things have changed over the last year. 

The median sales price in January of 2021 was $285,500, and in January 2022, it was $316,250. That’s an increase of about 13%. Meanwhile, the median sales price jumped from $321,000 to $362,000.  

In January of 2021, we had 1,991 new homes hit the market, while we only had 1,596 in 2022. This means fewer people are putting their homes on the market. 1,531 houses closed in 2021, while in 2022, our area had 1,443 closings.

“If you’re looking to sell, now might be the best time. ”

As for days on market, we had an average of around seven in January of 2021, and it’s the same now. However, this number is a little misleading. If you price your home correctly and work with a great team, you can easily sell your home in a day or two.

What does this all mean for you? We know interest rates are increasing, and buyers seem frustrated with rising prices. When rates do increase, prices will probably have to go down, so if you’re looking to sell, now might be the best time. Meanwhile, buyers will want to purchase a house before rates hike since even small rate increases hurt their buying power quite a bit. Are you interested in searching for available homes in the RVA area? You can access any MLS listing here: https://markadams.exprealty.com/

My team is currently sitting on 15 buyers desperate to buy a home before rates increase. If you are looking to buy or sell, please call or email us. We’d love to help you!

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/How+Sellers+and+Buyers+Can+Navigate+Our+Market+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/How+Sellers+and+Buyers+Can+Navigate+Our+Market+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Comparing today’s market to January 2021 and what the numbers mean for you.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Comparing today’s market to January 2021 and what the numbers mean for you.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Are You Prepared for a Home Emergency?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-you-prepared-for-a-home-emergency.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-01-24 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Are+You+Prepared+for+a+Home+Emergency_+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s a quick story about why it’s important to prepare for emergencies.

Today I have a story I wanted to share with you about something that recently happened to a friend of mine. (Disclaimer: Everyone is fine!) 

While my friend was out of town with his family, his house caught on fire. What’s worse is that his pets were stuck inside. Thankfully, the neighbors knew about my friend’s pets, and they were able to get the animals out safely before the fire department arrived. When Lisa and I heard about this, we thought, “Wow, we really need to get in touch with our neighbors!” Lisa reached out to them to ask how many pets they have in their homes, and she let them know how many we have in ours. This exchange of information could be very important if, God forbid, an emergency happened in your neighborhood.

“Always overestimate how much time you will be out of your home so that you can plan your temporary accommodations accordingly.”

Many years ago, Lisa and I had a pipe freeze in our house, and the whole place flooded. We lost nearly everything, including both of our computers, which held so much important data. At the time, cloud storage wasn’t available, but I can tell you now that we make sure to back up our important documents and information regularly. I can’t speak enough about how crucial it is to make sure your vital information is safe from fire or flood. I also encourage you to check out my video about making a digital home inventory, just in case. 

My final tip concerns your insurance company. When our house flooded, the insurance company told us we would be out of our home for about 3 months. It actually turned out to be 10 months! Thankfully, we were renting an apartment with a renewable, month-to-month lease. The bottom line: Always overestimate how much time you will be out of your home so that you can plan your temporary accommodations accordingly.

I hope these tips for preparing your home for a potential emergency are helpful. I wish you all a safe and happy new year, and as always, if you need any assistance with anything real estate-related, give me a call or send me an email. I’d be happy to help.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Are+You+Prepared+for+a+Home+Emergency_+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Are+You+Prepared+for+a+Home+Emergency_+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s a quick story about why it’s important to prepare for emergencies.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s a quick story about why it’s important to prepare for emergencies.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Our Tips For Reviving Your Home in 2022</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/our-tips-for-maintaining-your-home-in-2022.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2022-01-10 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Our+Tips+For+Reviving+Your+Home+in+2022+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here are our tips for maintaining and refreshing your home in 2022. 

Happy New Year! It’s the time of year when everyone is making a list of what they want to get done with their home, and I have some great tips to help you accomplish your goals. Lisa and I do this exercise every year, so we want to go over how we revive our home:

1. Wipe down your shower after every use. This will prevent mold from building up, so you won’t have to remove it later. 

2. Re-caulk your shower. Unfortunately, wiping down your shower won’t prevent the caulk from turning yellow. If you replace the caulk, you’d be surprised how new your shower will look. 

3. Spray your glass shower door with Rain-X every three months. This will prevent water and soap scum from sticking to your shower door. It will look brand-new all year round. 

4. Change your home decor every three months. Lisa changes our decor based on the season. Her tip for you is that instead of buying new pillows, she simply buys new pillowcases. This way, we get a fresh, seasonal look without breaking the bank.

“Subtle changes to your home can make it really pop. ”

5. Replace the front door mat regularly. These things don’t last as long as you’d think. If your mat is looking old, consider replacing it. 

6. Replace the mailbox and replace the post. It’s subtle, but little things like this can make a big impact on your home. 

7. Replace the pots for houseplants, and replace your picture frames. This tip is similar to changing pillowcases. You can make the details of your home seem new and exciting just by changing how they’re framed. 

8. Make sure the lightbulbs are the same type and color. This will make your home appear more cohesive.

9. Install switch plate covers. This way, you don’t have to replace the receptacle ever again. The convenience switch plate covers offer is unmatched. 

Hopefully, these tips gave you some ideas on how to breathe new life into your home in 2022. If you have a tip you’d like to share with me, leave it in the chat or send me an email. I’d love to share it with everyone else!

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Our+Tips+For+Reviving+Your+Home+in+2022+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2022/Our+Tips+For+Reviving+Your+Home+in+2022+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are our tips for maintaining and refreshing your home in 2022. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are our tips for maintaining and refreshing your home in 2022. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What We Accomplished in 2021</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-we-accomplished-in-2021.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Holidays</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-12-16 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here are some of our biggest highlights from a jam-packed 2021. 

Happy holidays! Lisa and I love this time of year because it gives us an opportunity to reflect on what we’ve accomplished. Not only that, but we learn from what we did to make next year even better. 

For example, one of our goals for 2021 was to build Lisa an amazing garden, and we accomplished it. Lisa wanted us to eat better, and our garden has been providing us with tons of vegetables. Since we share, all our neighbors are pretty happy with us, too!

If you’re like me, then you remember all those great meals you had as a kid that you  haven’t had in a long time. I wanted to spend more time with my mom this year, so I started going over to her home for dinner more often. We had some of the classic food from my childhood, but we tried some excellent new dishes, as well. 

I also had to go on many business trips this year. Typically, I do what I need to do for business and leave, but this year, I made an effort to explore each new area I visited. For example, I went hiking in Arizona, and the terrain was unlike anything I had seen before.

“Teaching shop has been the highlight of my week ever since I started doing it.”

Usually, Lisa and I aren’t big spenders, but I had been talking recently about how I wanted a new truck. When she took her truck to the dealership to be serviced, she found almost exactly what I had been looking for, and she surprised me with the vehicle when she came home. This wasn’t on our list of goals, but it was an awesome surprise and certainly a highlight of the year. 

Something that’s important to me and Lisa is service. Recently, I had the opportunity to help teach a shop class for a local school. I was super excited, and it’s been the highlight of my week ever since I started doing it. Helping kids learn something I love has been incredibly rewarding, and I look forward to teaching the class in the future. 

As we look forward to 2022, one of the highlights for Lisa and I will be our 32-year wedding anniversary. It’s hard to believe it’s been that long, but I’ve loved spending my life with her. 

However, that’s enough about us; let us know what you are looking forward to in 2022. Just give us a call or shoot us an email. We look forward to hearing from you!

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are some of our biggest highlights from a jam-packed 2021. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are some of our biggest highlights from a jam-packed 2021. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Real Estate Market Update to Round Out 2021</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-real-estate-market-update-to-end-2021.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-12-06 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/A+Real+Estate+Market+Update+to+Round+Out+2021.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s a brief end-of-year real estate market update for Central Virginia.

As we head toward the end of the year, I’m sharing how our real estate market is doing and where we’re headed in 2022. We’re going directly into the Central Virginia Regional MLS to look at some of the latest numbers.

Let’s start with the average sale price. At the beginning of 2021, it was at $321,733. It precipitously rose through the middle of the year, and we hit a high of $367,966 in the summer before dropping back down later into the year. Right now, it sits right around $359,000. 

The bottom line is that our lack of inventory is the cause behind these price increases. In January 2020, we sold 4,001 homes. In January 2021, we sold only 2,126. The big reason behind this is that there just weren’t as many homes available for buyers to purchase. That drove prices up, and that inventory doesn’t look like it will go back up anytime soon.

We don’t know where the market is going, but we do know that it’s definitely changing. The list-to-sale price ratio measures what homes have sold for compared to their original list prices. In January, we were a little over 100%. Then in May, we jumped up to 104%. Then it started to gradually go down, and now we’re at 101.5%. That’s a tell-tale sign of the market softening and changing. I don’t know where it’s going, but I do know one thing: Sale prices are very strong.

“If you’re a buyer, you can still take advantage of rates in the 3.2% range.”

Here’s the thing: I believe we’ll see the same type of activity as we go into 2022 based on the fact that there still aren’t a lot of available properties for sale. If you’re a seller, the positive is that you’re probably going to get a very high price for your house. We have data that shows it’s a great time to get your home sold for top dollar. If you’re a buyer, you can still take advantage of rates in the 3.2% range.

If you’re looking to sell and buy, how can you set it up so you’re successful? We’ve had a lot of success selling properties off-market. We found buyers for many of our sellers without having to put their homes on the market. These buyers can meet the seller’s needs in price and flexibility to give them the time to find their new home. This situation puts you in a great position as a buyer because your home is already sold. 

If you’re thinking about selling, I’d be happy to do a Comparitive Market Analysis and let you know what your home is worth today. I might already have a buyer in my back pocket who can give you what you’re looking for.

If you have any questions about these numbers, the market, or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/A+Real+Estate+Market+Update+to+Round+Out+2021.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/A+Real+Estate+Market+Update+to+Round+Out+2021.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s a brief end-of-year real estate market update for Central Virginia.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s a brief end-of-year real estate market update for Central Virginia.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Thanks for Coming To the Zoo With Us!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/thanks-for-coming-to-the-zoo-with-us.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-11-08 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Thanks+for+Coming+To+the+Zoo+With+Us.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here are some highlights and clips from our fifth annual zoo event.

Thank you for coming out to our fifth annual zoo event. We had a great time seeing all of our amazing clients and walking around the Metro Richmond Zoo. While we were there, we also collected a ton of food for Feed More. We put together a short highlight reel of the event. Check it out in the video above.

As always, give us a call if you have any questions. We’d love to help, and thanks again for coming out to the zoo with us.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Thanks+for+Coming+To+the+Zoo+With+Us.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Thanks+for+Coming+To+the+Zoo+With+Us.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are some highlights and clips from our fifth annual zoo event.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are some highlights and clips from our fifth annual zoo event.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Happy Thanksgiving From Mark Adams & Associates</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/happy-thanksgiving-from-mark-adams-associates.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-11-08 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Happy+Thanksgiving+From+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s why we’re so thankful for you as we reflect on this past year.

Thank you, thank you, thank you! Words aren’t enough to express my gratitude for all of you, but I’m going to try.

Lisa and I sit down every year around this time and think about the biggest blessings that have come our way over the last year. The last 12 months have been weird at best, and we know many business owners that are unfortunately no longer in business. 

Because of you, not only did we have a great year, but we thrived in this strange environment. We can’t thank you enough for your support. There are people that work for us who rely on us and have families, and there are other real estate-adjacent companies that rely on us as well. All of them have been positively affected by you and your trust in us.

“Your trust and support mean the world to us.”

We know how emotional it is to buy a house. It’s typically the single biggest investment you’ll ever make. Lisa has told me many stories of watching kids growing up in houses and it always brings us back to the time that we got to serve them. We love seeing the pictures and posts of your families on social media. Some of those young kids are now buying homes with us or referring us to their other family members and friends. 

For the past 21 years, most of our business has been referral-based. From the bottom of our hearts, thank you for that. If you need anything from us, real estate or not, feel free to reach out because we would absolutely love an opportunity to serve you in any way possible. We hope you have an amazing holiday season!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Happy+Thanksgiving+From+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Happy+Thanksgiving+From+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s why we’re so thankful for you as we reflect on this past year.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s why we’re so thankful for you as we reflect on this past year.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>When Will We Reach the Peak of the Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/when-will-we-reach-the-peak-of-the-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-10-05 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/When+Will+We+Reach+the+Peak+of+the+Market_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

MLS data is showing us that we’re likely near the peak of the market.&lt;/p.

&nbsp;

I get asked a lot about when we’ll know if we’re reaching the peak of this market. I have some statistics from our regional MLS that I want to share with you. I think they give us some idea of where the market’s headed:

**Average sales price.** In January of 2020, the average sales price was around $295,000. In January of 2021, the average sales price was $321,000. In September, the average sales price reached $357,000.

**Homes for sale.** In January of 2020, there were 4,000 homes available. In January of 2021, there were only 2,000. Inventory is really low. In September of 2021, there were still only 2,000 available, when there should normally be 4,000. That's why we continue to see prices go up.

**Days on market.** We had 49 days in January of 2020, 25 days in January of 2021, and 15 days in September of 2021. As far as days on market, it almost halved every step there. That's amazing, right?

&#8220;I think we’re very close to a peak in the market.&#8221;

**Average list-to-sales price ratio.** This is the statistic that I believe will show us where the market is going. In January of 2020, the average list-to-sales price ratio was 97.5%. In January of 2021, it was 100.2%. In September of 2021, it was almost 102%. However, in May of 2021, it was 104% and declined from then on. I believe that's a tell-tale sign that the market has started to change.

About two months ago, I noticed that we were having fewer showings and offers at the same locations and at the same prices. Those are all signs of buyer fatigue. Buyers are tired and fed up. It's a natural market cycle. Have we hit the peak? I think we're very close to it, but now's still a great time to sell your house for top dollar.

If you're thinking about selling or if you want to know the value of your house, feel free to give me a call. I'd love to help you look at your neighborhood data and learn what's going on to see if you can still sell at or above market value. I look forward to hearing from you.

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/When+Will+We+Reach+the+Peak+of+the+Market_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/When+Will+We+Reach+the+Peak+of+the+Market_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>MLS data is showing us that we’re likely near the peak of the market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>MLS data is showing us that we’re likely near the peak of the market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Over the Edge With Greg and NFM Lending</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/over-the-edge-with-greg-and-nfm-lending.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-09-17 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Watch as Greg Cowart rappels down the Dominion Power building.

&nbsp;

As you know, we recently participated in the Richmond SPCA’s “Over the Edge” fundraiser to raise money for the animals in our community. Those who reached the $2,500 fundraising goal were entered into the “Toss Your Boss” contest - if you hit a certain goal, you got to send your boss over the edge of the second tallest building in RVA. 

We reached and surpassed our goal! With your help, we raised $2,874. Lisa surpassed the team goal, guaranteeing herself a rappelling spot, but we decided it would be more fun to raffle Lisa’s spot off instead. We held a client and vendor appreciation event in July, and anyone who donated at least $25 was entered into the raffle. 

The winner of the raffle was Jesse Perrone, who works with our preferred lender, Greg Cowart of NFM Lending. (You might remember Greg from our pumpkin taste test video.) Instead of using the ticket for herself, Jesse decided she wanted to toss HER boss. The funny part was that she didn’t tell him! Instead, she put a lunch date with his wife on his calendar.

“With your help, we raised $2,874.”

He is always able to improvise quickly, and takes surprises very well. Check out the video above, starting at 0:54, where we tell Greg that he’s the lucky winner and see footage of him rappelling down the massive edifice. We’d like to give him a special shout-out for not only being a great and trusted lender, but a great sport, too.

If you have any real estate-related questions for us, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Watch as Greg Cowart rappels down the Dominion Power building.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Watch as Greg Cowart rappels down the Dominion Power building.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Ways to Find the Perfect Contractor</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-ways-to-find-the-perfect-contractor.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-09-08 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here are my top three methods for finding a great contractor.

&nbsp;

Let me guess: You need a contractor ASAP, but everyone you’ve called is already booked. Don’t worry. Here are three tips to help you find a great contractor:

1. Referrals. Reach out to your list of contacts, neighbors, and even people you know on facebook. If they’ve had contract work done recently, ask them about it. Was it done on time? Did they show up on time? Did they charge a reasonable price? These questions will help you get a feel for the contractor. Then, once you reach out to them, make sure they are licensed and insured. Every job is different, so depending on the work, licensing and insurance could be crucial. 

“If you need work done on your home, chances are I can refer you to a reliable contractor. ”

2. Call the supply house and talk to sales. Let me give you an example: When I renovated my house about eight years ago, the trim contractor I usually worked with wasn’t available. I called the lumber house, asked for their top salesperson, and asked them who they would recommend for trim carpeting. The contractor they recommended did a fantastic job, and I still refer him to my clients today. This story just goes to show, if you talk to the top salespeople in an industry, they can probably refer you to an excellent contractor. 

3. Talk to me. As you can imagine, I keep in touch with contractors pretty regularly as part of my job. If you need work done on your home, chances are I can refer you to a reliable contractor. 

Thanks a ton for visiting my blog. If you have any questions about today’s topic, or if you need a great contractor, please reach out to me via phone or email. I am always willing to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are my top three methods for finding a great contractor. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are my top three methods for finding a great contractor. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Meet Wilma Adams, The Newest Member of Our Family!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/meet-wilma-adams-the-newest-member-of-our-family.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-08-09 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Meet+Wilma+Adams%2C+The+Newest+Member+of+Our+Family!.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Find out how we adopted our new dog, Wilma.

&nbsp;

It’s been 9 months now since Sadie passed away, and we’ve been talking about getting another dog. Lisa’s really big on the adoption process, so I just wanted to share a bit about how we ended up adopting Wilma. We were expecting it to be easy, but it really wasn’t.

We went to about three different rescues, and they all do it differently. At some agencies, you have to find a dog you want before you fill out the application. For others, you’d fill out an application and they’d match you with a dog, and this was what we did for Wilma.

This time around it was pretty emotional. The rescue had matched us with Wilma, and we only had a certain amount of time to respond to get our appointment. By the time Lisa had seen the email, it was too late, and we’d missed the chance to meet her. That was tough. 

“I thought adopting a dog would be easy, but it wasn’t.”

Lucky for us, the other people had to cancel their appointment, so we got another chance to adopt Wilma! We learned from her foster mother, Brenda, who volunteers with Lab Rescue LRCP, that Wilma came in as an abandoned pup in pretty bad shape with her little sister Betty.

We’re super excited to have her, and we can’t wait to see what the cats think!

As you might already know, we recently made a commitment to raise funds for the Richmond SPCA. You partnered with us to help exceed our goal. We raised $2,844! Thank you so much for your generosity. Now we are making a different kind of commitment, one that will give us years of joy and companionship, by adopting Wilma!

As always, feel free to reach out to us with any real estate question you might have.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Meet+Wilma+Adams%2C+The+Newest+Member+of+Our+Family!.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Meet+Wilma+Adams%2C+The+Newest+Member+of+Our+Family!.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Find out how we adopted our new dog, Wilma.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Find out how we adopted our new dog, Wilma.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Pet Owners: You Can Still Sell for Top Dollar</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/pet-owners-you-can-still-sell-for-top-dollar.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-07-02 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Pet+Owners_+You+Can+Still+Sell+for+Top+Dollar.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Having pets in your home shouldn’t preclude you from a successful sale.

&nbsp;

Does having a dog or cat in your house while it’s on the market affect its saleability? In my opinion, yes, but here are a few suggestions to help you sell a home while having pets:

1. Neutralize the house the best you can. Remember that you get to decide when buyers actually go inside your property. Lisa and I have previously sold homes that had dogs and cats living in them, so we know that when you have animals, they’ll probably leave unwanted messes on the carpet every once in a while, and it’s important to take away those buyer objections. Also, get rid of any food/water bowls, toys, litter boxes, and clean the cat litter closet so there’s no evidence that animals live in the house. You want to set the stage when buyers walk through the door and, as I mentioned, take away any objections they may have. 

2. On showing days, remove your pets from the house. I know this isn’t always possible, especially if you’re at work and somebody wants to see your home. Sometimes we see sellers leave their dogs in a kennel or leave a note saying that their cat is in the house somewhere. It just depends on your situation. In a perfect scenario, though, I always say remove any animals from the house. I’ve been to showings with buyers who refused to take a good look at a house because a dog was inside and they were more concerned about that. Seeing this made me concerned enough to share this advice with my seller clients. If there’s any way you can get your pets out of the house during a showing, do it. 

“Even with animals, you can make your house look amazing.”

3. Have a friend, family member, or your Realtor do a sniff test of your home. I’m not saying it’s a bad thing that your house smells like an animal lives there, but other people might not find it very pleasant. If it does, shampoo the carpet, clean the floors the best you can, and stick some scented plugins into the walls. 

4. Remove dog waste from the yard. Buyers will want to take a look around, and if they see a bunch of droppings scattered about, that’s a big-time negative. 

Here’s the thing: Even with animals, you can make your house look amazing. You’re not trying to lie to buyers. You’re just trying to neutralize the house as much as possible so that when they come, you’re setting a positive stage instead of a negative one. 

If you’d like to know more about getting your house in the best shape possible so you sell for top dollar, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to help you in any way I can.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Pet+Owners_+You+Can+Still+Sell+for+Top+Dollar.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Pet+Owners_+You+Can+Still+Sell+for+Top+Dollar.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Having pets in your home shouldn’t preclude you from a successful sale. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Having pets in your home shouldn’t preclude you from a successful sale. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Data says it's great time to jump in!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/data-says-its-great-time-to-jump-in.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-07-02 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Market+Update_+Data+Facts.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here is your market update comparing data from 2020 to 2021.

&nbsp;

Today I want to give you a market update on what we’ve been seeing in the last 12 months. The information I’m sharing with you is coming directly out of the Central Virginia Multiple Listing Service. Let’s dive in!

Back in May of 2020, the median sales price was $265,000, and in May of 2021, it was up to $297,000 (a 12.3% increase!). Property values typically only go up by about 3% to 5% per year. That’s a seriously big jump! Single-family homes are up from $268,000 to $303,000 and condos went from $249,000 to $263,000.

“It’s still a really good time to put your house on the market.”

From May of 2020 to May of 2021, the average days on market has gone from 34 days down to 24 days, which is down by 29%. Homes have been selling quicker!

The percent of the original list price received in May of last year was 98.4%. The average is now 101%. If you’re a seller right now, you’re basically guaranteed to get your sales price. It’s still a really good time to put your house on the market.

Buyers, I know that some of you are discouraged about jumping into the market right now. All the industry experts are saying that property values are going to continue along this trajectory. One of the contributing factors to the continuing rising prices is that 70% of all homeowners right now have 50% or more equity in their houses. 38% of all homeowners actually have their houses paid off. That means that if something happens and they need to sell, they’re not going to lose money because they have so much equity. Even though it’s hard to get in the market right now, it may be even harder next year because property values are going to go up. Right now, you can take advantage of low interest rates.

Last year in May, we had 3,172 homes on the market. Now there are only 1,669. That’s down by 47%. Right now,  a lot of first-time homebuyers are flooding the market, and there aren’t as many people of the last generation who are selling their houses. That’s what’s creating the supply and demand issue.

Last year in May, our months of inventory was at 1.9 months. Now we’re down to just a month of inventory. This data is again telling us that if you’re a seller, it’s probably a really good time to get your house on the market and get the most money out of it.

If you have any questions or if you’re interested in knowing what your property value is, feel free to give us a call. We would love to help you out in any way that we can. Have a great day.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Market+Update_+Data+Facts.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Market+Update_+Data+Facts.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here is your market update comparing data from 2020 to 2021.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here is your market update comparing data from 2020 to 2021.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>We’re helping animals in RVA</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/were-helping-animals-in-rva.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-06-15 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+helping+animals+in+RVA+(2).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s why we’re partnering with the SPCA to raise funds for local animals.

&nbsp;Here are our fundraising pages with our stories and links to donate:Lisa&rsquo;s PageMark&rsquo;s Page

Today I am coming to you to talk about a cause that is near and dear to our hearts: animals. As you may know, we lost our sweet dog Sadie in November to cancer. We wanted to do something to honor her memory because she meant so much to us. 

Sadie was my garage and fishing buddy and she was Lisa’s best friend and garden helper. She was also a great friend to our cats: Clara, Fuller and Eli. She is greatly missed by our whole family.

To honor Sadie’s memory, Lisa and I decided to take part in the SPCA’s Over the Edge challenge and raise funds for the animals they care for.

Supporting the SPCA is a natural fit for us, but we really need your help and encouragement to reach our goals. You’ve always helped us support pet causes in a big way. Since 2009, you’ve donated around 15,000 pounds of pet food to our Meals on Wheels pet food drives, which provide meals for the pets of the seniors who receive meals from FeedMore.

“On average, an animal spends 22 days at the SPCA before being adopted.”

Lisa recently took a behind-the-scenes tour of the SPCA and was amazed at all they do to care for the pets there who are waiting for their forever homes. She visited the dog kennels and fell in love with a pit bull named Adam, saw the cat infirmary, the animal hospital, the adoption rooms, the laundry facilities, and even the bath stations. Check them out in the video above. She told me how clean it was and how good it smelled. For Lisa to say that, it really means something.

When you partner with us, your support will go directly towards caring for the dogs, cats and other creatures the SPCA takes in year after year. On average, an animal spends 22 days at the SPCA before being adopted.

Did you know that it costs $17 a day to care for each animal? A donation of just $25 provides bottle feeding for four infant kittens for two weeks and a $125 donation can pay the adoption fee for a senior pet, and you know how we love helping the seniors in our community.

With your donation, you may be helping a friend or family member’s next dog or cat in the process. As you can see, your support means a lot. You can make a huge difference by providing a day, a week, or even a month’s worth of care with your gift. 

We want to save them all, but we know we can only reach our goal with your love, support and encouragement. Please help us exceed our goals to make Sadie proud. Every dollar helps.

If you have any questions for us, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+helping+animals+in+RVA+(2).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+helping+animals+in+RVA+(2).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s why we’re partnering with the SPCA to raise funds for local animals.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s why we’re partnering with the SPCA to raise funds for local animals.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>We’re Sending You Homebot for Free!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/were-sending-you-homebot-for-free.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-05-27 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+Sending+You+Homebot+for+Free!.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We&rsquo;re sending you the Homebot app, so here are some of its great features.

&nbsp;

Do you want to know what your home is worth? Do you want to know how much equity you have in your house? I can provide those answers for free right now. For years, my team and I have been researching companies for an app that we could send to our clients for free that would tell them the value of their homes. We finally found it, and it’s called Homebot. 

Here are a few of its great features:

1. Home value. One tap shows you the value of your home. The app may not know about your home’s amenities, so you can also adjust the value higher or lower based on what your home includes. 

2. Your equity position. By the time the average American retires, 83% of their wealth comes from home equity. Homebot helps you keep track of your equity position.

3. Amortization chart. This tells you how much you would save on interest if you made extra mortgage payments. Personalized calculations can help you save money and pay off your loans quicker.

“This app has so many cool features that we think you’ll enjoy exploring.”

4. Rent estimation. If you’ve considered renting out your house or making it an Airbnb, the app will tell you how much you can charge for it. 

This app has so many cool features that we think you’ll enjoy exploring. They also have a feature where you can tap a button if you want more specific information about that part of the app. They even have features that can help if you’re thinking about buying a property.

Your house is the largest asset you’re ever likely to own, and Homebot can help you make informed decisions. It provides valuable market data and wealth-building insights. Homebot is free to you, and it’s coming to your email from us, so be on the lookout for it.

 

If you have questions for us about real estate or if we can help you in any way, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone, text, or email. We would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+Sending+You+Homebot+for+Free!.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/We%E2%80%99re+Sending+You+Homebot+for+Free!.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’re sending you the Homebot app, so here are some of its great features.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’re sending you the Homebot app, so here are some of its great features.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Crime Prevention Through Environmental Design</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/crime-prevention-through-environmental-design.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-05-11 06:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Crime+Prevention+Through+Environmental+Design.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Officer Mashburn is back to discuss CPTED and keeping your home safe.

&nbsp;

Today our special guest is back by popular demand: Officer Mashburn. The last time she joined us, she talked a bit about environmental design, and we thought it was fascinating, so she’s back to share more about it. 

CPTED is the term used within the police department, and it stands for Crime Prevention Through Environmental Design. It’s based on the theory that the proper design and effective use of the built environment can lead to a reduction in fear of crime and improvement in quality of life. 

“Lighting shows ownership.”

Many things are included in CPTED, but one of the most crucial is natural surveillance or landscaping. For example, homeowners should keep shrubs and trees maintained around their homes so they can see all parts of their house as they walk up to it from the street. Let’s say you have a large bush next to your house—if you keep it maintained, there’s less opportunity for someone to hide behind it. (Who knew the police had strategic ways they could tell us to landscape to keep safe!)

Lighting is another essential aspect, and we call it territorial reinforcement. Lighting shows ownership, and there are four main factors to it: the proper amount, high visibility low-glare, uniformity, and fixture type. Regarding uniformity, whatever lighting is chosen for the front, back, or sides of the home, we recommend that it illuminate that entire part of the house; we don’t want to see pockets of darkness. When choosing fixtures, ensure they direct light downward—don’t waste light by directing it horizontally, as that doesn’t cover anything. 

We look forward to having Officer Mashburn back again in the future. If you have any questions or real estate needs, please reach out to us via phone or email. We would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Crime+Prevention+Through+Environmental+Design.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Crime+Prevention+Through+Environmental+Design.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Officer Mashburn is back to discuss CPTED and keeping your home safe.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Officer Mashburn is back to discuss CPTED and keeping your home safe.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Our Team is Even More Important During a Hot Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-our-team-is-even-more-important-during-a-hot-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-04-21 06:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Why+Realtors+Are+Even+More+Important+During+a+Hot+Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s how our team can help you make more from your home sale.

&nbsp;

It’s an incredibly hot market right now, and it has some people wondering if they even need an agent in order to sell their homes. Though it’s possible to sell on your own, I highly recommend against it.

First of all, we build relationships. Most of our business comes through referrals, and we often work with past clients as well as their friends and family members. It speaks for itself—over the past 20 years, we’ve provided such great service that people consistently return or bring in others for us to serve. If we didn’t do a good job, we wouldn’t be getting that repeat business.

That’s not the only thing we offer; we also provide monetary value. Homes are getting so many offers nowadays that it can be difficult to determine which one is the best. The craziness of our market has created a lot of strange situations when it comes to offers, and we have the professional expertise to sift through and figure out which one works well for your needs.

“The bottom line is that our team holds an incredible amount of knowledge that allows sellers to find exactly what they need.”

Here’s a quick story that illustrates how we can help you: One of our best clients recently referred a friend to us. This new client was doing a for-sale-by-owner listing, and her property was in fantastic shape—however, her price tag was about $20,000 too high. It wasn’t selling, so we met with her to see what was going on and discovered that the photography was terrible. Additionally, her emotional investment in the home meant she was unable to make objective decisions when it came to offers. 

We came in, figured out what her home should actually be priced at, and took good pictures for the listing. Her property sold the very next week, and at a higher price than she could have gotten on her own.

The bottom line is that our team holds an incredible amount of knowledge that allows sellers to find exactly what they need. If you’d like to learn more about what we can do for your situation, or if you have any questions about real estate, feel free to reach out to us. Every situation is different and we strive to make the selling process as enjoyable and stress free as possible. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Why+Realtors+Are+Even+More+Important+During+a+Hot+Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Why+Realtors+Are+Even+More+Important+During+a+Hot+Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s how our team can help you make more from your home sale.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s how our team can help you make more from your home sale.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Reasons Why Selling Right Now Is a Good Idea</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-reasons-why-selling-right-now-is-a-good-idea.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-03-12 05:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/3+Reasons+Why+Selling+Right+Now+Is+a+Good+Idea.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Don&rsquo;t sell yourself short by waiting to put your home on the market. 

&nbsp;

We’re in the middle of a market I’ve never seen before in my two decades of real estate. Sellers are at a unique advantage as buyers are using enticing ways to get their offers accepted. We’re selling homes for well above asking price, and even having appraisal and inspection contingencies waived. 

You might be thinking, “Sure, that sounds amazing, but WHERE am I going to go if I sell my house right now?” I’m getting this question left and right, so I wanted to propose an option. Stick with me while I explain why you should simply move out. Your next dream home may not be available yet, but I have three reasons why you may not want to wait for it to come along to sell your current house. I know the idea of temporary housing doesn’t sound the most appealing, but I’ll tell you why it might be worth it to you. 

“Sellers are at a unique advantage as buyers are using enticing ways to get their offers accepted.”

First, we’re seeing homes sell for $10,000, $20,000, even $40,000 over the asking price. That alone is motivating people to list now. Beyond that, sellers are getting those prices without making any updates, which brings me to my second reason to sell now: Buyers are so eager right now they are willing to forgo inspections and/or they are waiving repairs. We’ve seen it happen with the last three of our contracts. This is saving sellers money and the headache of having contractors in and out of their house. I’ll leave you with the third and perhaps greatest reason to move right now: The proceeds from the sale will put you in the BEST possible cash position to buy your dream home. And isn’t that the goal?

If you’d like to know what your home could sell for in this market, or you have questions about temporary housing options, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to hear from you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/3+Reasons+Why+Selling+Right+Now+Is+a+Good+Idea.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/3+Reasons+Why+Selling+Right+Now+Is+a+Good+Idea.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Don’t sell yourself short by waiting to put your home on the market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Don’t sell yourself short by waiting to put your home on the market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Winter Sowing Vs. Winter Growing: What's the Difference?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/winter-sowing-vs-winter-growing-whats-the-difference.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-03-01 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Winter+Sowing+vs+Winter+Growing+What's+the+difference.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Lisa Adams joins me to teach us about winter sowing.

Lisa joined me today to share the next phase in her vision for our suburban garden. Since we don’t have a ton of land to farm on, she brought the idea of winter sowing to me, which is so easy to do, we just had to share it with you. Check out Lisa’s step-by-step demonstration in the video above.

So, what is the difference between winter sowing and winter growing, you ask? Winter sowing is essentially making a mini greenhouse to support seeds while they germinate during the wintertime. This differs from winter growing, where you plant directly into the ground or utilize a greenhouse or cold frame, in order to produce vegetables that are harvested in the wintertime. What’s great about winter sowing is that you probably already have most of the materials you need at home, aside from the seeds and potting soil, and it takes up very little room in your yard. The process is simple – you put your seeds in soil in a plastic milk jug, seal it, and then put it outside and wait for them to sprout. Then, come springtime, your plants are ready to go in the ground to flourish. The beets, radishes, and broccoli Lisa planted a couple weeks ago are already beginning to grow!

If you’d like to learn more about this method of growing, here is the Facebook group Lisa belongs to.

If you have any questions about real estate or would like more ideas for home projects like this, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Winter+Sowing+vs+Winter+Growing+What's+the+difference.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/Winter+Sowing+vs+Winter+Growing+What's+the+difference.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Lisa Adams joins me to teach us about winter sowing.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Lisa Adams joins me to teach us about winter sowing.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Calculate Your Home’s True Worth?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-calculate-your-homes-true-worth.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-02-12 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/How+Can+You+Calculate+Your+Home%E2%80%99s+True+Worth_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s how to get an accurate valuation of your home.

&nbsp;

Sellers: Zillow, Trulia, Realtor.com, Redfin, and every other estimated home value website out there is inaccurate. Heck, even your tax assessor’s office is inaccurate when it comes to valuating your home. Why? Because they use computer-automated programs to estimate its value.  

First and foremost, there are many factors that determine a home’s value—location, style, amenities, school district, etc. Knowing this, I’ll give you an example of how automated systems can make mistakes. Let’s say there are two houses, House A and House B, from the same neighborhood that were built at the same time (20 years ago) and are the same size: 2,000 square feet. The only difference between them is that House A recently had its kitchen and bathrooms updated and was sold about two years ago. House B, meanwhile, has never been resold since it was built and doesn’t have any upgrades. 

“If you give me a call, I’ll come to your house, take lots of notes, and compare it to other houses based on all the factors I’ve shared.”

When an automated system focuses on a certain area, it incorporates all the recent sales data. If it doesn’t know what House B initially sold for, it will use the data from nearby homes that have sold recently. If House A has upgrades, it stands to reason that it’s worth more than House B, but an automated assessment will give House B a higher value. Unfortunately, many people trust these assessments despite the fact that they’re wildly inaccurate. 

So how can you accurately calculate your home’s worth? Say hello to your friendly neighborhood Realtor! If you give me a call, I’ll come to your house, take lots of notes, and compare it to other houses based on all the factors I’ve shared. The thing is, I haven’t seen a real estate market like this in 20 years, and I’m not just saying that. There is very little inventory, and sellers are cashing in on the fact that interest rates are also very low, which means there are a lot of buyers but not enough houses for them all. 

If you’re considering selling your house in the next six to seven months, call me today so I can give you the very best estimate of its value. If you have any other real estate needs, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/How+Can+You+Calculate+Your+Home%E2%80%99s+True+Worth_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/How+Can+You+Calculate+Your+Home%E2%80%99s+True+Worth_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s how to get an accurate valuation of your home.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s how to get an accurate valuation of your home.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Shou Sugi Ban: Easy as Ichi, Ni, San</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/shou-sugi-ban-easy-as-ichi-ni-san.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-02-01 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/How+to+Do+Shou+Sugi+Ban.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s my recent project of trying the Japanese Shou Sugi Ban technique.

&nbsp;

Over the holidays, my wife Lisa asked me to build some raised beds for her new garden, and they turned out well. However, when I was done, she said they looked bright and new and wondered whether there was any way to treat them to make them appear weathered. She did some internet research and found out about an ancient Japanese technique called Shou Sugi Ban where you lightly char the wood to preserve it.  This technique is not only for garden beds, but any wood-working project, such as sheds, cabinets, etc.

“We think these garden beds turned out wonderfully.”

So, I went to Lowe’s and found an excellent torch tool that’s designed to burn weeds but works well with this technique. The torch cost about $55, was easy to use, and the tank of gas cost $25. I’m not a Shou Sugi Ban expert, but here are a few safety tips if you decide to try this project at home:


  Wear a good pair of safety glasses.
  Wear a secure pair of safety gloves.
  Stay away from the tank when you’re burning. This torch throws out a large flame, and you don’t want any explosions happening!


We think these garden beds turned out wonderfully. Watch me using the Shou Sugi Ban technique starting at 1:00 in the video above. 

If you have any questions about how I made these garden beds or concerning real estate, feel free to call or email me. I’d love to share this technique with you. Arigato! 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/How+to+Do+Shou+Sugi+Ban.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/How+to+Do+Shou+Sugi+Ban.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s my recent project of trying the Japanese Shou Sugi Ban technique.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s my recent project of trying the Japanese Shou Sugi Ban technique.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Highest Offer May Not Be the Best, and Here’s Why</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-highest-offer-may-not-be-the-best-and-heres-why.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-01-18 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/The+Highest+Offer+May+Not+Be+the+Best%2C+and+Here%E2%80%99s+Why.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s why the highest offer isn&rsquo;t always the best one.

&nbsp;

In a multiple-offer situation, why is the highest offer not always the best?

For our listings, we regularly see multiple-offer situations where buyers compete with each other to the point that they’re making offers above asking price. The problem with this is that in their contract, the buyer has the option to order an appraisal. The contract also states that if the home doesn’t appraise at the written sale price, they have three options:


  Ask the seller to reduce their price to the appraised value. 
  Negotiate a price somewhere in between
  Ask to be let out of the contract (if the first two options fail)


My team and I recently listed a property that snagged seven offers. The top two offers were $30,000 and $23,000 above asking price. The buyer behind the second offer, though, negotiated up front with the sellers that they would pay the difference between the written sale price and appraised value if it happened to be less. That was huge, and the buyer behind the first offer didn’t include that kind of contingency in it, which meant if the home didn’t appraise, they’d have a problem on their hands. When we did a comparative market analysis of the area, we discovered that the price that buyer offered didn’t support the comps, so that was likely where their deal would’ve ended up. In this case, the second buyer clearly had the better offer. 

As always, if you have questions about this or any real estate topic or would like to know what your home is worth in today’s market, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/The+Highest+Offer+May+Not+Be+the+Best%2C+and+Here%E2%80%99s+Why.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2021/The+Highest+Offer+May+Not+Be+the+Best%2C+and+Here%E2%80%99s+Why.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s why the highest offer isn’t always the best one.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s why the highest offer isn’t always the best one.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>January 2021 Richmond home price update</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/january-2021-richmond-home-price-update.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2021-01-11 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Friends and Clients —

The real estate market continues to surge ahead. However, clouds might be forming on the horizon for sellers. Let me give you the details:

1. Ultra-low mortgage rates

Throughout 2020, the popular 30-year fixed mortgage rate set 15 new record lows. 

It ended 2020 just one basis point higher than the latest record low and currently stands at 2.86%, a full percentage point lower than one year ago.

These ultra-low mortgage rates are driving an increase in demand. Unfortunately, sales are restricted due to…

2. Record-low inventory

There were just 1.28 million homes available for sale at the end of November, the last month for which we have full data.

That is down 22% from a year earlier. It is also the lowest inventory count since the National Association of Realtors began tracking this metric in 1982.

Unsurprisingly, home prices are shooting up thanks to strong demand and record low inventory.

The median price of an existing home sold in November was a staggering 14.6% higher than in November 2019.

If you’re worried this pace is unsustainable, you might be right:

3. A change in the market?

Some experts warn that home prices are overheating and that affordability is suffering.

They might have a point because, after five consecutive months of gains, closed sales of existing homes lowered in November. 

Similarly, after three straight months of record highs, homebuilder confidence in December dropped 4%. December mortgage applications also fell. 

So what does this all mean for you?

Well, things might get harder soon for home sellers.

Lower affordability could hurt demand, and the price growth we’ve seen over the past months might slow down, or prices might decrease like we started to see before the pandemic.

Fortunately, nationwide trends haven’t caught up to us yet in Richmond.

Demand is still very strong. If you were to list now, you could sell quickly and at top dollar.

If you’d like to get an idea of what your home is worth right now, you can use the following home value calculator, which is based on recent Richmond sales:

Enter your address here to find out what your home is currently worth

If you are considering selling while the current market lasts, give me a call at 804.237.8585. I’ve helped many people sell in these pandemic circumstances, and I’m here to answer your questions and help however I can.

If you have a friend or family member thinking about selling it would be my pleasure to earn their business. Don’t hesitate to call me and I promise to take great care of them.  

Have a great day,

Mark Adams
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The real estate market is golden for sellers right now.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The real estate market is golden for sellers right now.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: What Are Your Good Luck Superstitions?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-what-are-your-good-luck-superstitions.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-12-16 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q_+What+Are+Your+Good+Luck+Superstitions_+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

You may not be superstitious, but we’re at least a little ‘stitious!

We got together as a team to celebrate another successful year in business, in spite of all the curveballs 2020 threw our way. Although it was a great year for many reasons, you might be as happy as we are to say “good riddance!” to 2020. As our mindsets shift toward 2021, we want to bring about all the good fortune possible, so we reminisced on some superstitions from our childhoods. We figure that 2021 may need as many of these good-luck charms and superstitions as it can get, so we went ahead and performed a whole mess of them!

To start, Mark’s mom always prepared black-eyed peas to eat on New Year’s to bring good luck. He also eats an apple every day to keep the doctor away (would you call that luck or science?). Also, picking up pennies is something he still does to this day.

Chloe also recalls tossing pennies into a fountain as a kid for good luck, and on the first day of every month, she recites the words “bunny, bunny, bunny”—a twist on the classic “rabbit, rabbit, rabbit” superstition.

“People in Spain toast at midnight with 12 grapes in their glass, symbolizing 12 months of good luck for the new year.”

Rabbits are also a part of Amy’s good luck traditions. She carries a rabbit’s foot to rub for good luck, with much success; it’s brought about some clutch UVA basketball wins and even a surprise baby!

Lisa has a horseshoe from her grandfather that symbolizes luck, and tosses salt over her shoulder. She also knocks on wood, which is something you might do all the time, too, but do you know why? In Irish folklore, evil spirits live in the wood, so you must knock on it to deafen their ears to your wishes.

Lastly, we all decided to cheers to the new year. As it turns out, Spaniards toast at midnight with 12 grapes in their glass; each one is to be eaten to symbolize 12 months of good luck in the upcoming year.

Here’s to your good fortune in 2021! If we can help you with that, at least by way of your real estate needs, please don’t hesitate to reach out. Happy holidays to you and yours, and adios, 2020!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q_+What+Are+Your+Good+Luck+Superstitions_+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q_+What+Are+Your+Good+Luck+Superstitions_+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>You may not be superstitious, but we’re at least a little ‘stitious!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>You may not be superstitious, but we’re at least a little ‘stitious!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: How Can You Stay Safe This Holiday Season?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-how-can-you-stay-safe-this-holiday-season.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-12-07 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q_+How+Can+You+Stay+Safe+This+Holiday+Season_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Officer Mashburn shares some simple but important tips for holiday safety.

‘Tis the season to be jolly! Let’s prevent some criminal folly.

We stole some of Officer Mashburn’s time, but we promise it was for a good cause. She joined us to answer some questions about deterring crime during the holiday season. Curious what you could take away from her message? Check out our brief interview in the video above to learn some great tips on protecting your deliveries from “porch pirates,” as well as protecting yourself, your home, and your vehicle.

If you’re just looking for quick tips to snatch ‘n grab, here are the highlights:


  
    Leave special instructions for delivery drivers for where to place your packages; ask that they hide them behind outdoor furniture or leave them at a side door where they are less visible.
  
  
    Keep all of your doors/windows locked at all times! 
  
  
    Don’t leave valuables (shopping bags, presents, etc.) in your car. Take them inside.
  
  
    Leave your lights on, especially your outdoor lights. Sure, it might run up your electric bill, but on the plus side, Santa will have no problem finding your house!
  


Special thanks to Officer Mashburn for spending time with us and for serving our communities. Even during this busy time of year, we’ll be here to help with any real estate needs you may have. Happy holidays, and stay safe, friends!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q_+How+Can+You+Stay+Safe+This+Holiday+Season_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q_+How+Can+You+Stay+Safe+This+Holiday+Season_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Officer Mashburn shares some simple but important tips for holiday safety.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Officer Mashburn shares some simple but important tips for holiday safety.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Are You Thankful for This Year?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-are-you-thankful-for-this-year.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-11-18 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/What+Are+You+Thankful+for+This+Year_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The Mark Adams Team is grateful for so many things this year.

With the holidays approaching, it’s a great time to pause and reflect on what we’re grateful for. Today I’m joined by my favorite people, my team, to share what we’re thankful for this holiday season.

Amy is thankful to have been able to spend a lot more time at home with her family this year. She has also gotten to enjoy decorating her new home in Wintergreen. Her children have been very productive in making ornaments for their Christmas tree at the mountain house. These talented kiddos need their own Etsy account!

Chloe is grateful for many things that came from quarantine. She’s gotten to fulfill her dream of being a stay-at-home mom while also having a job—the best of both worlds. She’s also thankful for all the educators who have taken an impossible situation and made the best of it. Although homeschooling is challenging, she is glad to have a more active role in Joie’s education.

“We hope that you and yours have a truly happy Thanksgiving.”

Fall is Lisa’s favorite time of the year, and is grateful that she’s had the opportunity to spend lots of time with her animals in 2020. She’s thankful for her health and the ability to work from home with her husband (thanks to noise-canceling headphones). She was also given an unusual blessing in the fact that her brother and his family were able to spend more time with their mother, who passed away recently. The hospital allowed his whole family to be there with her, which isn’t typical these days. Also, Lisa is grateful for being able to spend time with friends over Zoom, take walks, and settle into a good book.

As for me, I’m thankful for my friends and family members. This time in quarantine has also given me an opportunity to not only spend more time at home, but also to enjoy the amazing garden my wife created where she’s grown some impressive pumpkins! One of the most critical lessons we’ve learned during quarantine is how important it is to be around people. Our team has missed meeting in person on a regular basis, so we really appreciate this time we’ve had together today.

Last, but not least, we’re all thankful for you! We’re so grateful for being able to serve such amazing people like yourselves. We hope that you and yours have a truly happy Thanksgiving.

What are you thankful for this year? Reach out to us and let us know—we’d love to hear about it!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/What+Are+You+Thankful+for+This+Year_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/What+Are+You+Thankful+for+This+Year_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Mark Adams Team is grateful for so many things this year.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The Mark Adams Team is grateful for so many things this year.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Our Blind Taste Test of All Things Pumpkin</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/our-blind-taste-test-of-all-things-pumpkin.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-10-15 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/videoplayback+(2).mp4</guid>
        <description>

In honor of fall, we’re (blindly) sampling savory pumpkin-flavored treats.

You may have heard of Blind Melon; please welcome Blind Pumpkin to the stage—a blind pumpkin taste test, that is! ‘Tis the season for all things pumpkin spice. We decided to take a break from work and go ALL in. Our buddy, Greg Cowart of NFM Lending, joined Mark and Amy to sample a spread of pumpkin-flavored novelties dished out by Lisa and Chloe (who may have snuck in some mind games). Check out this video to see our reactions, reviews, and see which of us has the sharpest palette.  And now that the sugar coma has worn off, we’re back to work, so don’t hesitate to give us a shout for your real estate needs!

As always, thanks for watching!

 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/videoplayback+(2).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/videoplayback+(2).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>In honor of fall, we’re (blindly) sampling savory pumpkin-flavored treats.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>In honor of fall, we’re (blindly) sampling savory pumpkin-flavored treats.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: How do you know if refinancing is right for you?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-know-if-refinancing-is-right-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-10-05 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+How+do+you+know+if+refinancing+is+right+for+you_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Given the market, should you stay in your home and refinance or just sell it?

Should you stay in your current house and refinance or should you prepare to sell it because the market is so attractive for sellers right now? 

There are a couple of questions you’ll need to ask yourself before you can make this decision:


  How long will I stay in the area? 
  What does it cost to refinance?


Once you have the answers to those questions, choosing which path is right for you should be a little easier.

Now let’s talk about the refinancing process. A good rule of thumb is that if you can get a good interest rate that’s 1% lower than your current interest rate, it might make sense to refinance. Typically, there are fees associated with refinancing. To find out what those fees are, just ask your mortgage company for a good faith estimate. That will have a list of all the fees associated with refinancing.

“If you can get a good interest rate that’s 1% lower than your current interest rate, it might make sense to refinance.”

Suppose that it’s going to cost $2,000 to refinance your house. In this scenario, you’ll get a 1% reduction in your interest rate, so you’d save $100 a month on your mortgage if you do refinance. In this case, it would take you 20 months to pay off the $2,000 investment. Ask yourself if it makes sense to even invest your money right now if it’ll take that long to recoup. It might make more sense to use that money to fix your house up so that when you get ready to sell in two or three years, you’ll get top dollar for it. It just depends on your situation.

If you’re still not sure about which path is right for you, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to share my advice about what exactly you can do to your house to get the biggest bang for your buck. I can also give you guidance about whether it makes sense to refinance your house instead. It’s my pleasure to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+How+do+you+know+if+refinancing+is+right+for+you_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+How+do+you+know+if+refinancing+is+right+for+you_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Given the market, should you stay in your home and refinance or just sell it?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Given the market, should you stay in your home and refinance or just sell it?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: Do You Know a Small Business Owner?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-do-you-know-a-small-business-owner.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-09-22 13:16:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Do+You+Know+a+Small+Business+Owner_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s how we’re helping other small businesses in our community grow.

Lisa and I started our business 21 years ago, and we quickly learned we had no idea how to run a small business. 

I sought out information at a real estate conference, where I met a coach who told me something that has stuck with me after all these years: “If you’re going to be a business owner, you need to make personal growth a part of your routine for the rest of your life.” 

“We will be offering training, networking, and much more.”

Two years later, I met another speaker who introduced me to the idea of masterminding. I learned how important it is to seek out other business owners in my field so that we can share experiences and learn from one another with the common goal of elevating ourselves and our industry. 

That’s the purpose of the group I started on Facebook, Intentional Business Owners of RVA. We will be offering training on business and personal growth, networking opportunities, and promoting your business connections via individual spotlights. If you are a small business owner, or know someone who is, we would love to have you be a part of our new community. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Do+You+Know+a+Small+Business+Owner_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Do+You+Know+a+Small+Business+Owner_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s how we’re helping other small businesses in our community grow.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s how we’re helping other small businesses in our community grow.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Want to know what your home is worth for free?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/want-to-know-what-your-home-is-worth-for-free.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-09-03 17:59:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Have you been thinking about what your home is worth lately?I wanted to let you know Richmond home prices are not dropping in spite of the seemingly never ending curve balls 2020 is throwing.

In fact, while inventory is down 40% nationally since sellers are likely hesitant to have buyers walk through their home, home prices are still strong (if not stronger).

Would you like to know what your home here in Richmond is worth for free? Call me at 804-237-8585. You’ll get my recommended home value opinion at no charge.

I just need a quick phone call with you to learn more about your home, along with any photos or videos you can send me (very important) by email, text, FB Messenger, etc. You’ll have a better idea of what a bank may value your home for a refinance, you can update your balance sheet, or you can just rest assured knowing what a buyer would likely pay today. 

Just last month, we worked with two families whose homes sold for 8% and 14% over the list price. You can imagine how pleased these clients were!

Interest rates are at record lows after the Federal Reserve lowered their lending rate and bank reserve requirements. This keeps home prices high since money is cheap for borrowers. 

History shows this amazing trend won’t go on forever. If you’re thinking about selling your home, this summer/fall may be your best chance to land your highest selling price.

I’m here to help with any real estate needs you have. Let me know if you have any questions. I’ll give you a well-researched and accurate answer so you can make the right decisions. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Have you been thinking about what your home is worth lately?I wanted to let you know Richmond home prices are not dropping in spite of the seemingly never ending curve balls 2020 is throwing.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Have you been thinking about what your home is worth lately?I wanted to let you know Richmond home prices are not dropping in spite of the seemingly never ending curve balls 2020 is throwing.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Your Friends Are My Friends</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/your-friends-are-my-friends.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-09-03 15:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Your+Friends+Are+My+Friends.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We want to assist your family and friends too. Help us help them!

You know by now that our team’s motto is “Where Relationships Are Key!”. We don’t spend hours a day on the Internet searching for strangers who want to buy or sell real estate. Our focus is on providing five-star service to our clients from start to finish and beyond in order to build positive, lasting relationships. Our goal is to treat people so well that they wouldn’t hesitate to suggest our professional care to their family and friends.

We learned a long time ago that if you take care of people, they’ll take care of you. So I’m asking you now: Will you help me help the people you love? 

If you have friends or family needing assistance with real estate, our team of specialists is ready to support them. We are just a call, text, or email away. We would love to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Your+Friends+Are+My+Friends.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Your+Friends+Are+My+Friends.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We want to assist your family and friends too. Help us help them!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We want to assist your family and friends too. Help us help them!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>August Is Hot, But the Market Is Hotter</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/august-is-hot-but-the-market-is-hotter.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-08-18 11:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/August+Is+Hot%2C+But+the+Market+Is+Hotter.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Our real estate market is red-hot for sellers right now.

Now, I’m not big on predictions when it comes to the real estate market, but I am big on giving you statistical data directly from our Richmond Metro MLS so you know what’s specifically happening right now. The three things you need to know before you get ready to sell are:

1. Average days on market. Right now, that number is 28 days in Richmond.

2. Average list-to-sale-price ratio. This is 100% right now, meaning that sellers are getting full price for their homes.

3. Inventory. We have only 1.3 months right now. To give you some perspective, a seller’s market is anything under six months and a buyer’s market is anything over six months. With just 1.3 months, we have an extreme seller’s market.

“I’ve never seen a market like this before.”

This checks out when it comes to what we’ve been experiencing with our clients. We’re working with one seller right now who got an offer that was 15% above asking price. Another seller got a sight-unseen cash offer of 8% over their list price. It’s a crazy market, and I’ve never seen anything like this in 21 years in the business.

If you’re even entertaining the idea of selling your home right now, I would love to give you some advice on how to proceed. Just give me a call or send me an email today with any questions you might have. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/August+Is+Hot%2C+But+the+Market+Is+Hotter.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/August+Is+Hot%2C+But+the+Market+Is+Hotter.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our real estate market is red-hot for sellers right now.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our real estate market is red-hot for sellers right now.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Could Your Home Be a Match for Our Buyers?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/could-your-home-be-a-match-for-our-buyers.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-30 13:25:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Could+Your+Home+Be+a+Match+for+Our+Buyers_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I’m digital door knocking to find homes for some of my buyers.

Today I wanted to share a new opportunity with you that I call “Digital Door Knocking.” As I’m sure many of you are aware, we are experiencing a shortage of inventory in the market right now. In other words, there are not a lot of homes for sale.

I’m doing things a little bit differently by telling you about some of the buyers we are currently working with and what they are specifically looking for.

First, we have this awesome couple with two kids who are looking in the Freeman school district. They want a home with four bedrooms, under $400,000, and most importantly, an in-law suite. 

Next, we have another couple who are first-time homebuyers with one child. They’re looking for a home in the Bellevue and/or Lakeside area with three bedrooms, two bathrooms, and under $350,000.

“If your home fits any of these descriptions, I want to buy your house.”

Another couple we’re working with are empty nesters who are moving back to Richmond. Location is not as important to them as the home. They’re looking for a contemporary house, and their budget is $1 million.

Finally, we have an amazing family of four who are looking for a home with five acres or more in the Louisa, Goochland, Hanover area. They need to have a basement and their budget is under $500,000.

If you’re a homeowner, have you ever had anybody knock on your door and say, “Hey, I want to buy your house?” Well, guess what? That’s what I’m doing right now. If your home fits any of the descriptions above, you need to give me a call today because I have a buyer for your house. 

If you have further questions for me, feel free to reach out via phone or email anytime. I look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Could+Your+Home+Be+a+Match+for+Our+Buyers_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Could+Your+Home+Be+a+Match+for+Our+Buyers_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’m digital door knocking to find homes for some of my buyers.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’m digital door knocking to find homes for some of my buyers.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: What Are the 3 Most Important Lessons My Dad Taught Me?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-what-are-the-3-most-important-lessons-my-dad-taught-me.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-21 16:09:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+What+Are+the+3+Most+Important+Lessons+My+Dad+Taught+Me_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

These lessons from my father shaped my view of the world.

Last month, we shared fond memories of our dads as a Father’s Day tribute. It got me thinking about the many lessons my father taught me that have shaped the person I am today. I wanted to share a few of my favorite lessons that I refer back to frequently. You may have heard these very same things from your father, mother, or mentor, or perhaps they will stir up other classic ‘dad phrases,’ which I hope bring a smile to your face.

1. If it’s worth doing, it’s worth doing right. When I was a young man, my father was a flooring contractor and used to bring me to work during summer break. He asked me to prep the floor so that he could lay the flooring when I was done. When I was finished, I went up to him and told him the floor was ready. However, he brought me back over to the floor and pointed out some dust that I had left behind. He told me that because I left the dust there, the glue wouldn’t stick and the floor would eventually come up. He proceeded to show me how to sweep the floor correctly. 

“I love my dad for giving me the gift of being able to live my life without fear.”

2. Always be teaching. My father was incredibly gifted with his hands. He worked on cars, lawnmowers, the house, and anything else he could get his hands on. He always brought me, my brother, and my sister along, too. As an adult, when I’m working with someone who’s never used a specific tool, I realize that it takes 10 times longer to show them how to do it rather than just doing it yourself. I have so much more respect for my father now because he was showing us how to do these things without hesitation when we were with him.

3. There’s nothing you can break that I can’t fix. I remember when I was about 20 years old, my father owned an excavating business and a piece of equipment called a backhoe. The problem with using this machine is that, in tight corners, the backhoe will hit things. He came up to me and let me know that I need to be cognizant of making tight turns if I want to avoid causing damage. Then he uttered these words: Son, there is nothing you can break that I can’t fix. He was basically telling me that it was OK to fail, and these words have shaped the lives of me and my siblings. I will never, ever forget that lesson, and I love my dad for giving me the gift of being able to live my life without fear attached to it.

I hold all three of these lessons with me every single day, and they have shaped my life in unimaginable ways. I’m glad to be able to pass them along here.

If you have any questions or real estate needs that I can assist with, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email today. I would love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+What+Are+the+3+Most+Important+Lessons+My+Dad+Taught+Me_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+What+Are+the+3+Most+Important+Lessons+My+Dad+Taught+Me_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>These lessons from my father really shaped my view of the world.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>These lessons from my father really shaped my view of the world.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Navigating Buying & Selling With Confidence</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/navigating-buying-selling-with-confidence.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-06 11:17:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Navigating+Buying+%26+Selling+With+Confidence.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s how we help our clients who need to buy and sell simultaneously.

I get this question a lot: “Mark, we want to buy a house, but we have to sell our current home first. We don’t want to risk carrying two mortgages, so how is this possible? The idea of an extra monthly payment is scary, but we have a solid strategy we’ve been using for years to ensure you don’t get caught in this financial bind. Check out this short video to see how we minimize the risk of buying and selling at the same time and give you the confidence to achieve your real estate goals. 

If you have questions about how we can help you buy a home, sell a home, or both at once, please don’t hesitate to reach out.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Navigating+Buying+%26+Selling+With+Confidence.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Navigating+Buying+%26+Selling+With+Confidence.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s how we help our clients who need to buy and sell simultaneously.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s how we help our clients who need to buy and sell simultaneously.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Are Your Favorite Memories of Your Father?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-are-your-favorite-memories-of-your-father.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-06-15 15:19:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+What+are+your+favorite+memories+of+your+father_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We’re sharing some fond memories of our dads.

We hope that you’re safe, healthy, and enjoying summer. In honor of the holiday, we took some time to reflect on our fondest memories of our dads. We hope these vignettes stir up some of your own special memories of the men in your lives that are fatherly to you. Happy Father’s Day! 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+What+are+your+favorite+memories+of+your+father_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+What+are+your+favorite+memories+of+your+father_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We're sharing some fond memories of our dads.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We're sharing some fond memories of our dads.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: Why Is Homeownership Better Than Renting?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-why-is-homeownership-better-than-renting.html.com/q-whats-going-on-with-the-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-06-09 11:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Why+Is+Homeownership+Better+Than+Renting_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Now is a great time to stop renting and become a homeowner. Here’s why.

When you own a home, you enjoy certain advantages that renters don’t get. Here are the top five reasons to buy your own home instead of renting:

1. You can make changes to the property. This could include changing the paint color, adding a big garden, and other projects that you just can’t do in a rental property.

2. You can write off interest annually. When you make your monthly payment on your mortgage, a portion of that goes toward interest, and you get to write that interest off on an annual basis.

4. Home equity. When you make your payment each month, you’re decreasing the life of the loan. The gap between how much you still owe and the value of your property is called equity, which can be used for multiple purposes.

5. Small business write-offs. If you own a small business and you’re using your home to operate that business, you get to write a portion of it off, which is especially nice given our current environment.

If you have any questions about this information or I can help you in any way, feel free to reach out to me.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Why+Is+Homeownership+Better+Than+Renting_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Why+Is+Homeownership+Better+Than+Renting_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Now is a great time to stop renting and become a homeowner. Here’s why.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Now is a great time to stop renting and become a homeowner. Here’s why.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: What’s Going on With the Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-whats-going-on-with-the-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-05-18 16:32:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Whats+Going+on+With+the+Market_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

These numbers show our market is a strong sellers’ market.

I’ve been getting a lot of questions about property values and recent home sale numbers. Today I want to address both topics with some hard data. For example, the median sale price in April 2019 was $259,000. This April, the median price was $271,538. People are still buying and selling homes right now. We’re taking every precaution to make sure all of our clients remain safe and healthy throughout the process. To learn more, watch the short video above.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Whats+Going+on+With+the+Market_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Q-+Whats+Going+on+With+the+Market_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>These numbers show our market is still strong.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>These numbers show our market is still strong.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Mark Adams & Associates Pizza Party</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-mark-adams-associates-pizza-party.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-24 14:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/The+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates+Pizza+Party.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Back before social distancing, my team got together to celebrate National Pizza Party Week. Check out our party in the video above!

One thing I love most about Superstars Pizza is that you can get pizza by the slice to customize your own bite instead of having to compromise with the rest of your family. When our team got together for our pizza party, we ordered eight equally delicious slices of all different types. We also dished out our individual pizza-eating quirks, and even tried a new approach to savoring a slice. We hope you get a kick out of our conversation!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/The+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates+Pizza+Party.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/The+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates+Pizza+Party.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our team got together a while back to enjoy some delicious pizza. Here’s our full conversation.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our team got together a while back to enjoy some delicious pizza. Here’s our full conversation.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What’s Happening in Our Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-happening-in-our-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-10 14:46:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Whats+Happening+in+Our+Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I’m sharing our latest real estate market statistics.

Yes, we’re all stuck at home, but happy spring anyway! For the last few weeks, everyone has been asking what’s going on in our real estate market and where it’s heading. Many people are getting their information online or through the news, but the info we’re sharing comes directly from our Multiple Listing Service (MLS). As of the recording of this video, in the last three days, there were 209 new listings on the marketplace, 214 homes actually went under contract, and 141 closed. So right now, we’re in a seller’s market. To learn more about our market, watch the short video above. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Whats+Happening+in+Our+Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Whats+Happening+in+Our+Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’m sharing our latest real estate market statistics.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’m sharing our latest real estate market statistics.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Glimpse Into My New Normal</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-glimpse-into-my-new-normal.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-09 13:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/A+Glimpse+Into+My+New+Normal.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s a light-hearted look at how I’m keeping my real estate business moving in these unusual times.

Everyone on the team is adjusting to our new work-at-home routines, including the pets. Today, instead of offering market statistics or future projections, I thought I’d share something on a lighter note. I’m giving you exclusive access into my new typical day at the office! Some of my morning rituals remain the same, but the commute sure looks different… Hope this leaves you smiling! 

If you have any questions about real estate, you know where to find me—at home, still working hard for our clients! Reach out by phone or email and I’d be happy to address your needs. Until then, stay safe, and make the most out of today!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/A+Glimpse+Into+My+New+Normal.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/A+Glimpse+Into+My+New+Normal.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s a light-hearted look at how I’m keeping my real estate business moving in these unusual times.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s a light-hearted look at how I’m keeping my real estate business moving in these unusual times.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Our Current Market: Is Now a Good Time to Buy or Sell?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/our-current-market-is-now-a-good-time-to-buy-or-sell.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-19 13:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Our+Current+Market-+Is+Now+a+Good+Time+to+Buy+or+Sell_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Hi there, Mark Adams here. I hope you and your family are staying well. I wanted to address the questions I’ve been getting lately regarding our current market.

“Mark, what’s really going on in the marketplace right now? Is now a good time to sell my house, or should we wait?

I’ve been in the business for 21 years now, and pushed through several market crises. We thrive during times like this because of the sturdy relationships we’ve built with lenders, attorneys, movers, and other service providers. We are prepared to continue serving you in the same capacity we always have.

“It’s still a seller’s market, but the interest rates will save you tons of money.”

The bottom line is, it’s still a seller’s market, and due to the low inventory, those that do put their house on the market are going to have less competition.

As far as buyers are concerned: yes, there is less inventory to choose from, BUT the interest rates are so attractive right now, so when you do find your dream home, it’s going to save you tons of money.

If you have any questions about your property or the buying/selling process, please do not hesitate to reach out. We are here for you, and ready to help in any way we can. Stay safe, and we look forward to serving you.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Our+Current+Market-+Is+Now+a+Good+Time+to+Buy+or+Sell_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/Our+Current+Market-+Is+Now+a+Good+Time+to+Buy+or+Sell_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We are prepared to continue serving you in the same capacity we always have.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We are prepared to continue serving you in the same capacity we always have.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Our Favorite Chips, in Honor of National Potato Chip Day</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/our-favorite-chips-in-honor-of-national-potato-chip-day.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-13 13:18:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/National+Chip+Day.mp4</guid>
        <description>

March 14 is National Pi(e) Day and National Chip Day. Today we’re celebrating in advance.

Did you know that March 14 is National Potato Chip Day? In honor of the occasion, I wanted to get together with my team to discuss some of our favorite salty, crispy, and crunchy treats.

My favorite are the classic potato sticks. They’re crispy, salty, and delicious.

Chloe’s are Pringles, which bring back fond memories of her mom sending her care packages filled with Pringles every summer at camp.

“What’s your favorite chip?”

Lisa brought Andy Capp Hot Fries, which she wasn’t introduced to until she met me. In addition to being crunchy and crispy, they add a little bit of spice.

Amy brought a local treat, Mama Saba’s Pita Chips. They are a scrumptious, slightly healthier alternative to potato chips. She also brought Dorito’s, which she used to put on a sandwich with mayo and country ham when she was younger and in school.

March 14 is also National Pi(e) Day, and I got a close-up view of one at 3:30 in the video above.

What’s your favorite chip? What’s your favorite pi(e)? Let us know in the comments. If you have any questions for us in the meantime, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/National+Chip+Day.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/2020/National+Chip+Day.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>March 14 is National Pie Day and National Chip Day. Today we’re celebrating in advance.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>March 14 is National Pie Day and National Chip Day. Today we’re celebrating in advance.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What You Need to Know About the New Construction Process</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-new-construction-process.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-24 12:39:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s some essential information to know if you&rsquo;ve considered buying a new construction property.

 

Amy “The Miracle Maker” Baker splits her time between the resale market and new construction. Since inventory is pretty slim, many are turning to new construction right now. Today she joins me to discuss why you need an experienced agent like her to help you navigate the new construction process.

What are the differences between buying new construction and resale homes?

In a new construction home, you get to choose the design, layout, and finishes that come in that home. With a resale home, you’re inheriting someone else’s home, including their landscaping and neighborhood.

What are the pros and cons of buying new construction?

The timeline for new construction can definitely be a downside; Amy has seen many delays in recent months, sometimes as long as three months!

“If you sign your name into a builder’s registry without including the name of an agent, you give up all representation.”

 What’s the difference between a production builder and a custom builder?

Production builders are cost-conscious; they’ll provide you with a few lot selections, floor plans, and finish packages to choose between. This keeps prices down and buyers from getting overwhelmed by all the options they have.

Custom builders give you a lot more choice over how the house is designed like your flooring, paint colors, trim, hardware, etc., so they involve a bigger time commitment.

What do people need to know about new construction purchases?

When buyers walk into a new construction site, there’s usually a salesperson or site agent there. That agent represents the builder, not you, meaning that if you write that person an offer on the new construction home, they’ll be negotiating for the builder and against you. So if you sign your name into their registry without including the name of an agent, you give up all representation.

That’s why you need to give agents like Amy a call before you begin shopping for homes; she’ll represent your best interests from the beginning to the end of the process.

If you have any questions about new construction, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’re happy to stand in your corner to help you achieve your goals.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s some essential information to know if you’ve considered buying a new construction property.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s some essential information to know if you’ve considered buying a new construction property.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Women Want on Valentine’s Day</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-women-want-on-valentines-day.html</link>
        
          <category>Fun Stuff</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-30 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2020/What+Women+Want+on+Valentines+Day.mp4</guid>
        <description>

What do women really want on Valentine’s Day? I brought together my favorite group of ladies: my team, Amy, Lisa, and Chloe. I’m going to ask them some questions, and their answers may enlighten you about what women want. 

Do your Valentine’s Day desires fall more in line with Hallmark or HGTV?


  Chloe: Is the food network an option? As long as he’s cooking for me.
  Amy: I like a little romance, but I also like projects. So I would want a pot for cooking, chocolates, perfume, or jewelry. 
  Lisa: For me it’s HGTV; I want those projects done. Make me something pretty.


“I brought together a group of my most favorite ladies in the world: my team.”

What’s the last thing you’d ever want on Valentine’s Day?


  Chloe: I do not want another singing card!
  Amy: Don’t buy me golf clubs; you can get me lessons, but not the actual clubs.
  Lisa: No fishing pole. I don’t want to go fishing, talk about fishing, or shop for fishing lures. 


What’s the perfect Valentine’s Day gift?


  Lisa: Something with whiskers… meow. 
  Chloe: I second that, but also pizza and champagne. 
  Lisa: Or a day trip. Even just shopping and lunch in another town nearby would be great.
  Amy: My family wants another puppy, so that would be the perfect family gift. I would also be happy to cook dinner for everyone.


I want to thank my favorite ladies for gathering to share their thoughts about Valentine’s Day. I hope you learned something, I know I did. Have a happy Valentine’s Day! 

If you have any questions about real estate, please feel free to reach out to us via phone or email. We would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2020/What+Women+Want+on+Valentines+Day.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2020/What+Women+Want+on+Valentines+Day.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>My team gathers to share their answers to Valentine’s Day questions.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>My team gathers to share their answers to Valentine’s Day questions.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Creating a Digital Home Inventory</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/creating-a-digital-home-inventory.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-22 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Creating+a+Digital+Home+Inventory+(2).mp4</guid>
        <description>

What if a fire destroyed your home? What if most of the damaged areas are unrecognizable? How would you prove what personal property was lost? I hope this never happens to you, but I’m sharing some tips for how to create a digital home inventory in case of any disastrous events. 

Theft, fire, and flooding can happen to homeowners. Do you know what you would need to provide to the insurance company to get those items replaced? 

First, using your phone or video camera, walk through your home and videotape each room, including every wall. This way you can show an insurance adjuster what your home looked like before the claim. Then take pictures of electronics, (front and back) with the serial numbers in clear view. Take photos of the appraisals for jewelry, silver, expensive eyeglasses, artwork, tools, and any valuable collectibles.

Remember: Anytime you bring home a new laptop, computer, or anything of value, be sure to snap a photo of the serial number right on the box. Keeping the receipt is a great idea, too. 

Lastly, upload your digital photo album to your online storage service. We use Dropbox, but you could use any photo storage site. Google Photos, iCloud, and Photobucket are common choices. Don’t use Facebook, as we don’t want to give burglars any ideas. 

Don’t forget to add photos to your digital home inventory each time you make a new, inventory-worthy purchase. The more information you provide to the insurance adjuster about a specific item, the better your chances to get it replaced with an item of the same value. Also, while you’re taking photos of your property, make sure to take one of the most valuable things of all: your pet! 

If you have further questions about  digital home inventories or real estate in general, please feel free to reach out to me by phone or email. I would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Creating+a+Digital+Home+Inventory+(2).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Creating+a+Digital+Home+Inventory+(2).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’m sharing tips for how to create a digital home inventory and why this is crucial.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’m sharing tips for how to create a digital home inventory and why this is crucial.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Include Your Home in Your New Year’s Resolutions</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/include-your-home-in-your-new-years-resolutions.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-06 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Include+Your+Home+in+Your+New+Years+Resolutions.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Happy New Year! I hope the new year is starting out wonderfully for you. You know about New Year’s resolutions, but have you ever considered including your home in them? 

At the beginning of the year, my wife and I make a list of all the things we want to accomplish in or on our house that year. Everything from larger projects like adding a porch, to smaller things like painting a room. Typically, your home is the single largest investment you’ll make. Maintaining your home truly helps you get an exceptional return when it comes time to sell. 

I receive calls from people frequently asking what’s the best improvement someone can make to get the highest return on investment. Generally, it’s kitchen and bathroom improvements. At the same time, not all investments will bring the same return. A fence, patio, or a shed, for example, are “use” items, which means you get to use them, but you don’t necessarily get a full return on that investment.

“Maintaining your home truly helps you get an exceptional return when it comes time to sell.”

Here’s what I recommend: Once you decide which projects you want to do, write them down. Make sure this list is in a place where you’ll see it regularly. When you see this list on a regular basis, you’ll be more inclined to get those projects done. Also, studies show that writing something down helps you remember it better. 

If you’re concerned about which projects you should do, give me a call or send me an email, I’d be glad to share which project will give you the biggest bang for your buck. Have a fantastic 2020!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Include+Your+Home+in+Your+New+Years+Resolutions.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Include+Your+Home+in+Your+New+Years+Resolutions.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’m sharing why you should include your home in your new year’s resolutions.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’m sharing why you should include your home in your new year’s resolutions.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Happy Holidays to You From Mark Adams & Associates!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/happy-holidays-to-you-from-mark-adams-associates.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2019-12-15 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Happy+Holidays+to+You+From+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates!+(3).mp4</guid>
        <description>

The holiday season has officially arrived. We hope you enjoy this wonderful time of year and make some fantastic memories with your family and friends. We wanted to take a moment to thank you for your continued support. We love helping people make their real estate dreams come true, so thank you for working with us.

This may be a busy time of year, but we are always here to help you and answer any questions you may have. Give us a call or email us!

In case we don’t hear from you, have a Happy New year!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Happy+Holidays+to+You+From+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates!+(3).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Happy+Holidays+to+You+From+Mark+Adams+%26+Associates!+(3).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The holiday season has officially arrived. We hope you enjoy this wonderful time of year and make some fantastic memories with your family and friends.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The holiday season has officially arrived. We hope you enjoy this wonderful time of year and make some fantastic memories with your family and friends.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Is NFM Lending?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-is-nfm-lending.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-24 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/What+is+NFM+Lending_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m here with Greg Cowart from NFM Lending to help me answer some questions I’ve received lately about mortgage lenders and loan products in the market. But first, what’s so special about NFM Lending?

Greg says, “What makes NFM Lending different from other mortgage companies is that we’re local; I’ve been doing mortgages in Richmond for 18 years. We focus on the purchase process, so we assist people who are buying homes. About 95% of what we do is walking someone through the process of buying a home and all the hurdles that commonly come up. So, when people choose us they’re choosing our experience, we work with a team. They’re choosing the fact that the team is going to give wonderful service all the way through, and they’re also choosing a smaller mortgage model, which allows for greater control and superior results.”

“When searching for the right mortgage lender, when you go with a well-known brand name, you’re also often getting things you don’t want such as bureaucracy, slowness, excuses, and excessive rules. NFM Lending is where a lot of experienced loan officers are going because they allow us to run our branch our way. I have the autonomy to create systems, to hire, to market myself, and create an experience that I wouldn’t get if I worked for one of the big brand name banks.”

“About 95% of what we do is walking someone through the process of buying a home.”

One of the things I appreciate most about Greg is that if a client comes to him and he can’t service them in the correct product, he’ll point them in another direction. 

Another question we get often is, “Are online mortgages something people should consider?”

According to Greg, “Online is an option, we’re seeing many industries moving in that direction. Most mortgages are five to six loan programs. They’re fairly standard from company to company. One of the things you’re accepting when you choose an online lender is their distance. You’re choosing someone who isn’t face-to-face, so you cannot as easily get ahold of them if something happens. Therefore, there’s a bit more lack of accountability. I generally find that the internet lenders don’t have as much experience, and they are also a lot more of a bureaucratic process, where the person you initially talk to may not be the one you work with all the way through. 

“Rocket Mortgage is a brand you may have heard of. They’re one of the first lenders to move heavily into a national online presence and buy heaps of advertising. It’s the same product we offer, it’s just going through an online platform, it’s more of a call center experience. We have the same computer systems, the same easy application process, we just haven’t marketed ourselves that way. At the end of the day they’re in Arizona and Cleveland, they’re not local to your community, Realtor, or client.”

If you have any other questions about NFM Lending or anything else concerning real estate, please reach out to me via phone or email, I would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/What+is+NFM+Lending_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/What+is+NFM+Lending_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’m here with Greg Cowart from NFM Lending to answer your questions about mortgage companies.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’m here with Greg Cowart from NFM Lending to answer your questions about mortgage companies.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Reasons to List During the Holidays</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-reasons-to-list-during-the-holidays.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-11 14:44:58 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Listing+During+the+Holidays.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I want to share three advantages to listing your home during the holidays:

1. Low inventory. During this time of the year, inventory is especially low, and there are not many admirable homes on the market. Most people wait until the beginning of the year to list their home, so there’s less competition. 

2. Motivated buyers. We don’t have any “window shoppers” out right now—we have buyers.

“During this time of the year, inventory is especially low.”

3. Home presentation. Your home never looks as nice as it does during the holidays. For example, my wife enjoys getting out the holiday decorations and making the house look incredible.

If you’re thinking about selling your house, don’t hesitate to give me a call. I’d be glad to come by and see if it makes sense for you to list your home during the holidays. If you have any questions feel free to call or email me. I’d love to help you in any way I can! 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Listing+During+the+Holidays.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Listing+During+the+Holidays.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’m sharing my three reasons to list your home on the market during the holidays.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’m sharing my three reasons to list your home on the market during the holidays.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>We Would Love to Serve Your Real Estate Needs</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/we-would-love-to-serve-your-real-estate-needs.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-04 14:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/We+Would+Love+to+Serve+Your+Real+Estate+Needs.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here’s the thing: I could go on and on about how wonderful our team is, but I’d rather share what some of our past clients have said about us:

Joey and Oliver said, “The team really treats you like family. They are so efficient and very helpful. They’ll take the stress away from buying or selling your home.”

Adeet said, “Amy Baker made sure the deal went smoothly despite some unexpected turns along the way. She was able to refer me to great people in our local area to help out with all aspects of the deal after closing.”

Cindy said, “Mark and his team are incredible. No one likes the process of selling their home, but they made it as painless as possible. They gave me a list of things to do they thought would make my house more attractive to buyers. There was no pressure, and my house sold over asking price in one weekend.”

“Everyone on our team has a passion for helping and serving others.”

George and Nancy said, “They did so much more than sell the house—we never expected the process to be so fast and painless.”

These were just a few people we’ve had the pleasure of serving over the last 20 years. Everyone on our team has a passion for helping and serving others.

If you have any questions about buying, selling, or anything to do with real estate, reach out to us. It truly would be our pleasure to serve you in any way that we can. 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/We+Would+Love+to+Serve+Your+Real+Estate+Needs.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/We+Would+Love+to+Serve+Your+Real+Estate+Needs.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What makes Mark Adams & Associates stand out among other real estate companies? Find out today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What makes Mark Adams & Associates stand out among other real estate companies? Find out today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Is 2019 the Best Time to Sell?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/is-2019-the-best-time-to-sell.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2019-09-19 14:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Is+2019+the+Best+time+to+Sell+My+House_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Many sellers are wondering whether 2019 may be the best time to list their homes, and the truth is that it very well may be. Homes are selling quickly and for top dollar—with homes in good condition often earning more than asking price. 

This is partially thanks to our interest rates, which, after dropping significantly since last year, have made buyers extremely eager to make a move.

However, these conditions won’t last forever. Home prices have been steadily on the rise since 2012, and they’re going to have to stabilize sometime. Experts say that time is drawing near. 

“We can’t be sure when the market adjustment will hit Richmond, but we can be sure that our current market holds great opportunities for buyers and sellers alike.”

The bottom line is that now is the time to act. We can’t be sure when the market adjustment will hit Richmond, but we can be sure that our current market holds great opportunities for buyers and sellers alike. 

If you have any other questions, would like more information, or would like to learn more about how I can help you take advantage of today’s market conditions, please give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon. 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Is+2019+the+Best+time+to+Sell+My+House_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Mark+Adams/Videos/2019/Is+2019+the+Best+time+to+Sell+My+House_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>2019 may be the best time to sell your home. Here’s why.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>2019 may be the best time to sell your home. Here’s why.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To Our Blog</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Mark Adams</author>
        <pubDate>2019-08-28 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Our market remains busy, and it’s still an opportune time to command a high price selling your home.  

We know what’s happening in Richmond and the surrounding areas, specifically pertaining to home values, that will directly affect you.

So, we’ll be posting two monthly video messages on this blog to keep you updated.  

They will be valuable and useful in helping you stay on top of what’s happening in the community.

Check back because content will be coming soon!

We’re excited to keep you updated on what’s happening in Richmond and the surrounding areas!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type=""/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our monthly messages will provide you with market updates, tips, and other educational information having to do with our market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mark Adams</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our monthly messages will provide you with market updates, tips, and other educational information having to do with our market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Mark Adams</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Mark Adams</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Mark Adams & Associates - your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
